welcome to category five technology TV
欢迎来到五类科技电视
it's so great to have you here in 2019
它是如此之大， 有 你 在 这里在2019年
as we kick off the year this this week
因为我们 本周开始这一年
we're gonna be looking at how to rip
我们要看看如何撕裂
episodic DVDs so if you got some DVD
如果你有一些DVD，那么情节DVD
sets in your stocking this week this
本周你的袜子里有这个
this year then you're gonna be able to
今年你就可以 了
copy those to your plex media server for
将它们复制到您的plex媒体服务器
example we're gonna talk all about it
例如， 我们将谈论 它
we're gonna show you how to do it and
我们将告诉你如何 做到这一点
and why I think we should also talk
为什么我认为我们 也 应该 谈谈
about our favorite moments from 2018
关于 2018年 我们最喜欢的时刻
we definitely should reminisce yes I
我们绝对应该回忆起我是的
think that'll be coming up to stick
认为这将会成为 现实
around our live recordings are trusted
我们的现场录音是值得信赖的
only to solid-state drives by Kingston
仅限金士顿的固态硬盘
technology revive your computer with
技术使您的计算机恢复活力
improved performance and reliability
提高了性能和 可靠性
over traditional hard drives with
超过传统的硬盘驱动器
Kingston SSDs category 5 TV streams live
金士顿SSD类5类电视直播
with Telestream wire cast and nimble
使用Telestream 线材铸造和灵活
streamer tune in every week on roku Kodi
roku Kodi 每周都有流光调
Plex and other HLS video players for
Plex 和其他HLS视频播放器
local show times visit category-five dot
本地节目时间访问 类别 - 五点
TV category 5 TV is a member of the tech
电视类别 5电视 是该技术的成员
podcast network if it's tech it's here
播客网络，如果它是技术它在这里
cat5 TV slash TPM and the international
cat5电视 斜线TPM和 国际
association of internet broadcasters
互联网广播公司协会
cat5 TV slash i a happy new year to all
cat5电视斜线， 祝大家新年快乐
nice to see you thanks for joining us
很高兴见到你感谢加入我们
this week again this feels like the
本周 再度 这种感觉 就像
first time we've been live in awhile
我们第一次住了 一段时间
because we had last week technically off
因为我们上周在技术上关闭了
which was a unique experience we don't
这是我们没有的独特体验
normally do that so not often hope
通常 这样做，所以不常希望
everybody enjoyed the the Christmas
每个人都喜欢圣诞节
musical fun I meant to watch it and I
音乐乐趣 我想看它和我
forgot isn't it funny how well I mean it
忘了我的意思不是很好笑
was it was Boxing Day right when it went
它是什么时候它是拳击日
to air and I was I had about 30 people
空气，我是约30 人
in my house I had created a turkey
在我的房子里我创造了一只火鸡
dinner and I was serving it up and we
晚餐，我正在服务，我们
were just about to sit down for dessert
正准备坐下 来吃甜点
when when the show went up yeah so I
什么时候节目上升，是的， 所以我
could stop it with the chat room and
可以与聊天室制止 ，
just say hi and I did see you pop in and
只是打个招呼， 我确实看到你流行了
say oh it's shoulder
说哦，它的肩膀
I didn't watch I hope that you had a
我没看，我希望你有一个
wonderful Christmas and a wonderful new
美妙的圣诞节 和一个美好的 新
year and and you know here's to the the
一年，你知道这里的
greatest year ever 2019 it's gonna be a
2019年最伟大的一年，它将是一个
good one
好一个
looking back on 2018 do we have any
回顾2018年我们有没有
favorite moments moments here at
最喜欢的时刻时刻在这里
category five TV that you guys can think
五级 电视，你们能 想到 的
of and I'd encourage you to think of the
和我鼓励你 想到 的
same and comment below your favorite
在你最喜欢的下面和评论相同
moments of 2018 here on category five TV
这是 第五 类 电视 的2018年
which one of you is this first I will go
你们哪一个是第一个我会去的
first I would say right off the hop I
首先， 我会说出我的跳跃
would say Marsh man's guest appearance
会说Marsh 男人的客串
and my liveing eight hours to join us
和我的生活八个小时加入我们
here in our Canadian studio meeting the
在 这里 我们的加拿大工作室 会议
marvelous mrs. Marsh man mm-hmm
奇妙的夫人。 沼泽人 mm-hmm
definitely top of my list as well yeah
绝对是我的首选，是的
but that's my number one that wasn't
但这 是我的第一个不是
here you weren't here you were you were
在这里你不在这里你是不是你
off gallivanting in the woods yes I was
在森林里哄骗我是的
what was freezing my butt off what
什么让我的屁股冻结了什么
favorite moments of 2018 do you have
你有2018年最喜欢的时刻吗？
here at the studio I think I have two
在工作室， 我想我有两个
that are tied for first okay the first
首先 是第 一个好的并列
one that popped my mind was the block
突然出现的是块
chain interview we did with Robert
我们与罗伯特做过连锁采访
Koenig mm-hmm I loved that interview
Koenig mm-hmm我 喜欢那次 采访
that totally changed my knowledge of the
这彻底改变了我对这个的了解
block chain took me to the next level of
块链把我带到了下一个 层次
amateur nests and and I was like hey I'm
业余的巢，我就像嘿，我
not just a newbie anymore I'm you know
不只是一个新手了，我知道你
amateur and I've taken some of that
业余的我已经采取了一些
knowledge from the interview and I've
来自面试的知识和我
had conversations with people even at
甚至在 与 人交谈
Christmas yeah we got talking about the
圣诞节是的，我们谈论 了
blockchain with my family and you know
与我的家人区块链，你知道
talking about other uses for the
谈到其他用途
blockchain not just cryptocurrency
区块链不仅仅是 加密货币
because like ours crypto currencies like
因为像我们的加密货币一样
Bitcoin stomach no there's other stuff
比特币胃没有 其他的东西
mm-hmm
毫米-HMM
and when I started explaining to them
当我开始向他们解释时
and you know the idea of like produce
而且你知道喜欢产品的想法
and not having all these recalls and you
没有所有这些召回和你
know then like when I raise the question
当我提出问题时就知道了
to him about why not use it for
他为什么不用 它
passports they're going oh that's cool
护照，他们要去哦，这很酷
mm-hmm oh we could talk yes I like it
mm-hmm 哦，我们可以说 是我喜欢它
and I was like I told my family on
而我 就像是告诉了我的家人
blockchain
blockchain
we are thick with knowledge we had a lot
我们拥有丰富的知识，我们有很多
of great interviews a lot of great
伟大的采访了很多 伟大的
presentations here on category-five over
这里介绍的类别五 以上
the past year that's definitely a
过去的一年绝对是一个
highlight for me as well and having
对我来说也很重要
back a couple of times and we're gonna
背个几次 ，我们要去
see him again in in 2019 as a crypto
在2019年再次见到他作为加密
correspondent as well I have to say one
通讯员我也要说一句
of my key points of 2018 not to do so
我 2018年的关键点不要这样做
much with the show but just thinking of
很多与节目，但只是 想
how the community viewers and even our
社区观众甚至是我们的观众
local community have come together to
当地社区 聚集在一起
support us and I think about how an
支持我们， 我想 的是如何
anonymous viewer sent us a ninja flame
匿名观众向我们发送了一个忍者火焰
video recorder to supplement our entire
录像机补充我们整个
broadcast process and now the video
广播过程和现在的视频
quality is better because of that and
由于 这个 原因 ， 质量更好
we're able to do so much more and how
我们能够做得更多， 如何做得更多
our local music Pro the music store in
我们的本地音乐专业音乐商店
town has gratis loaned us wireless
小镇免费借给我们无线
microphones so now we're moving around
麦克风所以现在我们四处走动
the studio and changed the show it has
工作室并改变了它的节目
absolutely changed and and now we're I'm
绝对改变了，现在我们就是我
thinking about how okay we can set up a
考虑我们如何 设置 一个 好的
set over there and we can just walk over
坐在那里，我们可以 走过去
and just turn the camera and we can do
然后转动相机 就可以了
this and that it's so much more freedom
这就是它的自由度
for us and and so just having community
对我们而言，只是 拥有社区
come together both our community on the
把我们的社区聚集在一起
show and the community here locally
秀和这里本地社区
supporting category-five has been
支持五类 已经
something that a you know that's a big
你知道这是 一个很大的东西
highlight for me can I add to that and
对 我而言 ， 我可以添加到 那个 和
it's the same line but switching to
这是同一条线，但切换到
discord for me yes huge for for
对我来说不和谐是非常重要的
community like I feel and I mean I feel
像我一样的社区，我的意思是我的感受
surrounded by friends all of the time
一直被朋友包围
now for example when I was doing the OS
现在 例如当我在 做 OS时
on my computer yes right and I was
在我的电脑上是的，我是
sitting there thinking for an iota of a
坐在那里思考一个iota
second I could do this alone and then
第二，我可以单独做到这一点
Garbi popped in and and between the two
突然出现的Garbi并与 两者 之间
of us
我们
mostly Garvey I managed to install a new
大多是加维 我设法 安装 了一个新的
OS on my computer which I don't have on
我的电脑上的操作系统，我 没有
me right now but that wouldn't have
我现在但不会 有
happened without discord and when you
没有发生龃龉 ， 当你
use the Bookface either because you hate
因为你讨厌而使用Bookface
rain it's taught us up to be like what I
下雨它教会我们像我一样
do people like hashtag like right yeah
人们 喜欢hashtag就像是的
and for those of you who are well what's
并为那些 你很好的人
this discord that she's talking about if
如果 她正在谈论这种不和谐
you look over there
你看那边
just past a Jeff you see what looks like
刚过杰夫你会看到什么样子
a chatroom and that's our discord server
一个聊天室， 这是我们的不和谐服务器
so you can join that through our website
所以你可以 通过我们的网站 加入
and there's there there are links on the
而且也 有有联系的
interact menu but what I love about that
互动菜单，但我喜欢这个
is you say switching to discord
你是说转向不和谐吗？
more like we've supplemented our
更像是我们补充了我们的
community with discourse IRC is still
话语社区IRC仍在
active I see the foo there and the foo
活跃的我看到那里的foo和foo
it's nice to see you the foo is in fact
很高兴见到foo实际上是这样的
communicating on discord via our old IRC
通过旧的IRC进行不和谐的沟通
chatroom so they're actually in IRC the
聊天室，所以他们实际上 在IRC
old way of doing things so we haven't
做旧的方式， 所以我们没有
replaced that we've supplemented it made
取而代之的是我们补充了它
a bridge and I wrote some code to be
一座桥，我写了一些代码
able to communicate between those two
能够在这两者之间进行沟通
servers and it's now one great community
服务器，它现在是一个伟大的社区
and its really helped to grow our
它 真的有助于我们的成长
community and the ability to communicate
社区和沟通能力
throughout the week and it really is
整个星期，它确实是
improved really notices because before
之前改进了真正的通知
with the chatroom you know it would be
与聊天室， 你知道它会
active during the show there'd be a few
在演出期间活跃的有几个
people throughout the week but now
整个星期的人， 但 现在
discord zop of people are on all the
所有人都不和谐
time
时间
yes it's yeah oh great gwg has taken
是的，是的哦，伟大的 gwg 已采取
offense to the fact that I call IRC the
因为我把IRC称为IRC这一事实
old way but to be fair was I used ire
旧的方式， 但公平是我使用了 愤怒
see when I was about this big I had a
看我什么时候这个大我有一个
full head of hair
满头发
IRC was before social media I had mIRC
IRC在社交媒体之前我有mIRC
and that was the application that I used
这就是我用过的应用程序
I mean it is old-school you got to admit
我的 意思是你要承认这是老派
and now you know we just we've been able
现在你知道我们刚刚我们已经 能够
to bridge that and make it make the
桥接它 并 使它成为
community even better
社区甚至更好
Jeff any other fond memories of 2018
杰夫对2018年的任何其他美好回忆
with cat5 yes specifically STEM show
与 cat5 是特别 STEM节目
with my daughter oh yes I loved doing
和我女儿一起哦，是的，我喜欢这样做
that that was was that in 2018 that was
那是 2018年的那个
the 21 that was episode 548 it was like
那是 第54集的第21 集
spring ish March April I believe no that
春天是三月四月我不相信
would have been 2017 no I looked that up
本来2017年我没有看， 截至
earlier really yeah I went through the
早些时候真的是啊我 经历了
show so oh you're right you're right
这样表明你是对的， 你是 对的
absent you I've got that recorded I was
没有你， 我有记录我
right no I had it mixed up with because
对不，我把它混淆了 因为
I was trying to remember when we had the
我试图记住我们何时拥有
kids on the show and I was thinking yeah
在节目的孩子，我想 是的
our March Break special that we did in
我们春令特殊，我们没有在
21 17 yes because she was on that as
21 17是的，因为她就是这样 的
well yes so that was her boombox now
是的，所以这就是她的 音箱
this was right when she had the the
这是正确的， 当她有了
gendell the Jen doll from smart girls
来自 聪明女孩的仁娃娃
yes and the fact that she was coding on
是和她正在编码的事实
it she still plays with it awesome I
它依旧玩得 很棒我
love it and it was so much fun watching
喜欢它 ，它 看起来很有趣
her just pick it up
她只是捡起来
use it on the tablet and start coding
在平板电脑上使用它并开始编码
and she with such a great job
她的 工作 非常 出色
that's a nominal job and now since that
这是名义上的工作，现在就是这样
time she's done commercials on Facebook
她在Facebook上做广告的时间
nice got that girl way to go kiddo
很高兴得到那个女孩去的方式
yeah ha ha another fond memory for me
是的，哈哈，对我来说是另一个美好的回忆
Jeff this was with you and I on the air
杰夫，你和我在一起
we did a review of the Edifier hard
我们 很难对漫步者 进行审查
12:10 tea speakers yes your hair moved
12:10茶叶扬声器是的， 你的头发动了
my hair your hair yeah the base from
我的头发你的头发是的 基地
these speakers made his hair below blown
这些扬声器使他的头发低于吹
Trump amazing that was that was a
特朗普令人惊讶，那是一个
highlight for me that was good also
对我来说也很重要
musically yeah the rap was she's ooh hey
在音乐上 是 的说唱是 她的哦嘿嘿
yes did that microphone was fun amazing
是这样做， 麦克风很有趣惊人
and got a great response on YouTube
并在YouTube上得到了很好的回应
surprisingly YouTube's usually really
令人惊讶的是，YouTube通常都是
hard on us but no it was all thumbs ups
苦 了我们 ，但没有这一切都竖起大拇指 起坐
because you let two girls talk oh there
因为你让两个女孩说话 哦
you go that's what I was I have to say
你去那就是我 要说的
though I think I have the most fun
虽然我觉得我最有趣
though with your questions yes those are
虽然你的问题是肯定的
always like solid shows for me yes don't
总是喜欢坚实的节目对我来说是的
always be a highlight I love the fewer
永远是我喜欢的亮点
questions I enjoyed learning to solder
问题我喜欢 学习焊接
and the way again going back to our
再一次回到我们的路上
community how the community made fun of
社区如何取笑社区
me but in a constructive criticism kind
我， 但在建设性的批评中
of way right to help me to learn more
正确的方式来帮助我了解更多
and more to do a better job at soldering
以及 更多在 焊接方面 做得更好
so now I understand more about how it
所以现在我更了解它是怎么回事
works right I know what the rosin does
工作正常我知道 松香的作用
and I know how I'm much much better at
而且我知道我的表现要好得多
it I'm still not a great solder er but
它我仍然不是 一个伟大的焊接工 但是
I'm learning and the community really
我正在学习社区
helped me with that mm-hmm any other
帮我与 MM-HMM任何其他
highlights for you well when we did the
当我们做到 的 时候，我们会 为您亮点
retro pie yes I was on my list out oh
复古派是我在我的名单上 哦
yes I wasn't here but I loved watching
是的我不在这里，但我 喜欢看
it and then well and then that followed
它然后很好 然后接着
up with doing the Odroid go with Marsh
做Odroid跟 Marsh 一起去吧
man the handheld yes which again like
男人 掌机是的再次喜欢
that that line of idea for retro gaming
那复古游戏的想法线
for me like that episode and then this
对我来说就像那一集然后这个
next episode which is gonna catapult me
下一 集即将弹射我
because I got one for Dave for Chris
因为我为戴夫买了一个给 克里斯
contestant
选手
and so I haven't assembled it or brought
所以我没有组装或带来
it to you it's like the next step for me
它对你来说就像是 我 的下一步
which is great ad yeah that's awesome
这是 伟大的广告是的 ，这是太棒了
and those are both examples of stem and
而 这些都是 干的 两个 实施例和
projects that we did ourselves right
我们做得 对的项目
that you participated in that we
你参加了 我们
actually built retro gaming stuff
实际上建立了复古游戏的东
exactly from a handheld to an actual
完全 从手持设备 到实际设备
retro pie which is like you think about
复古馅饼， 就像你 想的 那样
classic Nintendo games and classic Sega
经典的任天堂游戏和经典的世嘉
Genesis games and all those kinds of
创世纪游戏和所有那些
things on a Raspberry Pi and we built
Raspberry Pi和我们建造的东西
that mm-hmm
那mm-hmm
again it's funny you've gone from like
你又变得很 有趣了
uber beefed up VR to handheld retro feel
uber加强VR以手持复古的感觉
the whole spectrum
整个频谱
I did get my VR in 2018 nice so that
我确实让我的VR在2018年很好，所以
didn't happen on the show we need to get
我们需要得到 的节目没有发生
it on the show we need to get it on the
它在节目中我们需要得到它
show yeah I got my computer I built the
显示是的我有我的电脑我建了
computer in 2017 didn't did a new story
2017年的电脑没有做过新的故事
about the VR and like and then got my
关于VR和喜欢然后得到我的
tax return and yes no no I can't five oh
纳税申报表是的，不，不， 我不能五 哦
yes that's right yes
是的，是的，是的
what is the name another thing that I've
名称是什么， 我已经 另一件事
really enjoyed and thinking of the the
真的很享受 和思考
retropie and just all of the single
retropie和所有的单身
board computers that we've had on the
我们已经拥有的电脑
show
节目
lots of unboxings lots of reviews we've
很多拆箱很多评论我们都有
done the giggle scores love the double
做了傻笑分数爱双
scribe and we're learning how each of
抄写员，我们正在学习每 一个
these single board computers performs
这些单板计算机执行
against one another which to me is
对我来说是对的
exciting because up until a year and a
令人兴奋， 因为 直到 一年和一年
half ago realistically there was just
一半以前现实中只有
Raspberry Pi
树莓派
yeah there were other boards out there
是的还有其他板
but really in the market there was just
但真的在市场 上 就是这样
the Raspberry Pi and now there are so
在树莓派，现在有 这么
many much more powerful single board
更强大的单板
computers to the point where we're we're
电脑到了我们所处的地步
probably a couple of iterations away
可能需要几次 迭代
from being able to use one as a desktop
从能够使用 一个作为桌面
computer and and that has been a real
电脑和那是一个真实的
highlight for me yep any final thoughts
为我突出任何最后的 想法
on 2018 I know of one that
在2018年我知道 一个
well it may have been end of 2017 but
好吧，它可能已经结束了2017年但是
but I do it comes to mind because we're
但我想到了，因为我们是
talking about we are and everything but
谈论我们 是和 所有的事情
and I think it still counts because it's
而且我认为它仍然很重要， 因为它是
in my mind it's within the past year and
在我心中 它是在过去一年内
a bit okay but we did tour the Starship
有点好，但我们确实参观 了星舰
Enterprise that is - that was 2017 2017
企业即 -  2017年2017年
up mm-hmm so a little off on my timing
的MM-HMM 所以 在 我的时间 有点 过
but in my heart it comes back to me
但在我的心里，它 回到 我身边
every day and I think it's fresh to me
每一天，我 认为这对我来说很新鲜
because stage nine was shut down by CBS
因为第九阶段被CBS关闭了
and so you know I it's still a part of
所以你知道我仍然是其中的一部分
my 2018 being able to live that boyhood
我2018年能够度过那个少年时代
fantasy of standing on the Starship
站在星舰上的幻想
Enterprise and traveling around walking
企业和 四处走走
around on the starship we have time for
在星舰上 我们有时间
one more one more okay so remember we
还有一个更好， 所以 记住我们
did the review of those tablets and then
做了那些平板电脑的评论然后
Jeff brought in there was word sync and
杰夫带来了词同步 和
I bought a boogie board sync and then I
我买了一个冲浪板同步然后我
dropped it on the floor and then get
把它放在地板上 ，然后 得到
affixed well and I kept saying that I
贴得 很好，我一直说我
would call them all today on my lunch
我 今天 午餐时会打电话给他们
break
打破
I called them yes talked to a guy named
我打电话给他们是 和 一个名叫的人 谈过
Chris exact situation hi Chris yeah he
克里斯确切的 情况你好克里斯 是的他
was like yeah it sounds sincere and that
就像是的， 这听起来很真诚
is a problem with our case it actually
它实际上是我们案例的一个问题
is an open corner just when you have
你有一个开放的角落
your sink with you because I was calling
和你在一起，因为我在打电话
from work and I didn't have it with me
从工作中我没有和我在一起
mmm it doesn't work right now um he's
嗯，它 现在 不起作用， 他是
like just uh read off the I guess
像刚才 呃读出了我的猜测
product ID to me and I'll send you
产品ID给我，我会发给你
anyone he's just like straight up
任何他都喜欢的人
sending me anyone's yes I know yes I
送我 任何人是的我知道我是
know did you even have to play the I'm
知道你甚至不得不扮演我的角色
Sasha Rickman card no mention you on the
Sasha Rickman卡没有提到你了
show tonight fantastic man
今晚表现出色的男人
see that's the kind of tech support that
看到那种 技术支持
love it that we need in this world and
喜欢我们在这个世界上所需要的
companies that stand by their products
坚持 产品的公司
like that even when admittedly it was
这样， 即使 承认这是
your my fault I said I'm like I tried to
我的错， 我说我就像我试过的那样
protect this thing against me I bought a
保护这 件事不要我，我买了一个
case it didn't work and he said if we're
如果它没有用，他 说如果我们的话
working on that so it's a known flaw in
努力工作， 这是一个众所周知的缺陷
their protective case that's truly if
他们这是 真的，如果 保护套
you buy the additional component of the
你买了额外的组件
protection that is supposed to save it
应该保护它的保护
from draw right it doesn't actually save
从绘制 右边它实际上没有 保存
it from drops it's not Sasha it's not
从它下降 它不是 Sasha它不是
Sasha proof I really should be just a
Sasha证明我真的应该只是一个
walking commercial
走路商业
it makes sense to me though I mean
虽然我的意思是 对 我有意义
there's two sides to that but if I
这有两个方面，但如果我
bought a waterproof case right and then
然后买了一个防水套
I submerged my thing and it leaked and
我淹没了我的东西，它泄漏了
it got destroyed then I would expect
它被摧毁然后我会期待
that right proper tech support would say
正确的技术支持 会说
yeah we'll send you another one that's a
是的，我们会送你 一个 又 一个，这是一个
flaw so that's good thank you Chris
这很好， 谢谢 Chris
awesome awesome okay so tonight we've
太棒了真好，所以今晚 我们已经
got a fantastic show planned for you
为你准备 了精彩的 节目
we're going to be yeah we're gonna be
我们将 是啊，我们要扮演
learning how to rip episode ik DVDs
学习如何翻录 插曲ik DVD
which I'm really excited about this is
我感到非常兴奋 ，这是
something that we've really needed to do
的东西， 我们真正需要做的
because questions keep coming up on
因为问题不断 涌现
YouTube recently I feel like we've done
YouTube最近 我觉得我们已经完成了
this no really yeah huh we've we've
这不是 真的，是的， 我们已经
learned about ripping DVDs and some of
学会了翻录DVD和一些
what we're gonna learn tonight is redone
我们 今晚 要 学到的东西是重做的
got to do that but a lot of questions
必须这样 做，但很多问题
stem from that video and those are what
源自 该 视频，那些是什么
we're gonna set out to answer tonight
我们今晚准备回答
and and admittedly several years have
并且不可否认几年了
gone by since Kelsey and I did that
自凯尔西以来，我就这样做了
recently I removed elementary OS from my
最近我删除了我的 基本操作系统
work computer so my production computer
工作电脑所以我的生产电脑
where I do all my programming I ripped
我所做的所有编程都在哪里
it out of there and I took the step and
它走出 那里， 我迈出了一步
I installed Linux Mint latest and
我最新安装了Linux Mint
greatest version you know that I was
你知道我最棒的版本
impressed with Linux Mint here on the
这里对Linux Mint印象深刻
show really you know I'm a debian guy
显示你真的知道我是个 坏人
but I I do like the ease of the Ubuntu
但我确实喜欢Ubuntu的易用性
architecture and the the infrastructure
架构和基础设施
that they've created and so Linux Mint
他们已经创建了Linux Mint
was really a nice step away from
真是一个很好的一步
Ubuntu's interface while still giving me
Ubuntu的界面仍在给 我
the feel of like the matei I'm using
像 我正在使用 的 matei 的感觉
cinnamon but that that kind of I don't
肉桂，但那种我没有
want to say retro but I like that
想说 复古，但 我喜欢那样
paradigm of like a start menu if you
如果你喜欢开始菜单的范例
will yeah Linux it's the applications
将是Linux它是应用程序
menu or you know it just feels more the
菜单 或者你知道它只是 感觉 更多
way that I'm used to using a computer so
以前我习惯使用电脑的方式
I've been using that for several weeks
我已经使用了几个 星期了
now and I found that Linux Mint is
现在，我发现Linux Mint是
really it performs great it works better
真的，它表现得更好，效果更好
than Elementary did on my system I have
比基本在我的系统 我有
a brutally awesome system 96 gigs of ram
一个残酷的令人敬畏的系统96演出的公羊
24 cores 2 Xeon processors so
24 核 2个 Xeon处理器
most of that run yeah well this is my
大部分运行是的，这是我的
production system at work so running
生产系统在工作中如此运行
Linux on it is just a no-brainer but
上Linux它只是一个没有脑子 ，但
then I've got three screens in front of
那么我就在前面 的 三个屏幕
me and elementary oh and they finally
我和小学哦，他们终于
fix this after I'd been running it for
在 我运行 之后解决这个问题
so long but you can't drag things from
这么久但 你不能拖东西
one monitor to the other without this
没有这个，一个监视器到另一个
massive gap in between the screens so
屏幕之间存在巨大差距
there is this like ridiculous gap
这就像荒谬的差距
between the screens and you couldn't fix
屏幕之间你无法修复
it and the reasoning was because some of
它和推理是因为一些
my to two of my monitors are horizontal
我的 两台显示器都是水平的
the one in the middle is turned vertical
中间的那个是垂直的
okay so because of that vertical it was
好吧因为 那是垂直的
completely messed up
完全搞砸了
needless to say Linux Mint out of the
不用说Linux Mint了
box worked flawlessly installing the
盒子完美无缺地 安装了
Nvidia drivers flawless and and just
NVIDIA驱动无瑕， 只是
operating it over the past three four
在过去三四年中经营它
weeks has been brilliant so if so I say
周 如此辉煌所以如果是这样我说
that you know in my production
你在我的作品中知道的
environment with everything that I do at
环境 与我所做的一切
work it's all done now on Linux Mint and
在Linux Mint上 完成所有工作
if you're looking for a Linux distro I
如果你正在寻找 Linux发行版我
think that it's one that is definitely
认为这是肯定的
you know up there and that's one that I
你知道那里，那就是我
think that I'm pleased with that with
认为我很高兴有 与
that transition for sure that is cool
那个过渡肯定 很酷
mhmmm we've tried so many different
嗯， 我们尝试了很多不同的东西
Linux distros not to say any are you
Linux的发行不是说你没有
know that yeah it really is with Linux
知道是的，这真的是 Linux
it's it's a they're flavors you try the
这是 他们 尝试的 味道
one you know that works for you and that
你知道哪一个对你 有用
one right now is working for me you like
一个人现在正在为你工作，你喜欢
the mint oh I do I never used to I never
我做的薄荷 哦我 从来没有习惯过
used to I do now they've come a long way
我以前习惯他们已经走了很长的路
just quickly before we take a short
在 我们做空 之前很快
break I just want to say thank you to
打破我 只想说声谢谢
all of our patrons who have been
我们所有的顾客
supporting category 5 TV you can check
支持5类 电视，你可以检查
out more at patreon.com slash category 5
更多来自patreon.com斜杠类别5
it's a great way to support category 5
这是支持5类的好方法
TV this is free family-friendly episodes
电视这是免费的家庭友好 剧集
of tech TV every single week and we do
每个星期都有科技电视 ，我们这样做
more than just tech you recognize Jeff
不仅仅是技术越多，你认识 杰夫
from new every day it's a faith
每天都是新的，这是一种信仰
broadcast that we brought that we share
我们带来的广播分享
with you every single week we have we're
我们每个星期都和你 在一起
getting back into the pixel shadow and
回到像素阴影和
doing some video gaming there's there's
做一些视频游戏就有了
so much great content there but
那里有很多很棒的内容 但是
definitely the episode ik week to week
肯定是一周到一周的情节
of category 5 technology TV is if that's
第5类技术电视就是这样的
flagship show and it's always you know
旗舰秀，它总是你 知道
we we try to make this as accessible and
我们尝试将其设为可访问和
family-friendly and free and it's thanks
家庭友好和免费，谢谢
to our patrons and those who support
我们的 顾客和支持者
category five that we're able to do that
第五类，我们能够 做到这一点
so we thank you for that
所以我们感谢你
again patreon.com slash category five
再次patreon.com削减类别五
and with you know wrapping up the
和你一起知道收拾
Christmas season the shopping season
圣诞季节购物季节
thank you to everyone who used our
谢谢所有 使用我们的人
partner links as well to do your
合作伙伴链接以及做 你的
shopping throughout the year you know
你知道全年购物
it's not just a Christmas thing but
这不仅仅是圣诞节的事情
throughout the year if you're gonna be
如果你要成为全年的话
shopping online go to our website
在线购物访问我们的网站
category five dot TV click on support us
在支持我们 五级点 电视点击
and you'll see our partner links and
你会看到我们的合作伙伴链接和
there you're able to shop through our
在那里你可以 通过我们的购物
partners Amazon eBay all the different
合作伙伴亚马逊eBay 各有不同
stores you can think of think geek gear
店你能想到的想到怪胎齿轮
best yeah there's a ton on there and and
最好的 是，那里有很多，而且
other partners that we love and and and
我们喜爱的其他合作伙伴
support as well and they give us a
也支持他们给我们一个
commission on the sales so all you have
销售佣金，所以你有
to do is just go through our website and
要做的只是 通过我们的网站和
that's a great way to support us as well
这也是 支持我们的好方法
so that we can really be strong in 2019
这样我们才能 在2019年真正变得强大
I want to see category five grow and we
我希望看到第五类增长，我们
are growing to the point where we had
正在发展到 我们所拥有的地步
trouble with one of our servers today
今天我们的服务器的 一个麻烦
because our MySQL server was completely
因为我们的MySQL服务器是完全的
capped out there were so many requests
限制了这么多请求
on the server so you know these are
在 服务器 上， 所以你知道这些
things that we deal with here want to be
我们在这里处理的 事情 想成为
able to have the resources in place to
能够拥有 适当 的资源
be able to grow at the same rate as our
能够以与我们相同的速度增长
viewing audience which can be tough when
收视观众可以很艰难的时候
you give it away for free so for those
你免费赠送给那些人
of you who support us thank you for
支持我们 的 你们，谢谢你们
those of you who have considered
那些考虑过的人
supporting us and you haven't yet please
支持我们，你还没有 取悦
follow those links and those are some
按照这些链接，这些是一些
great ways to support us or just message
支持我们或只是消息的好方法
our community and they'll share some
我们的社区，他们会分享一些
other ways to to become a part of it as
其他方式成为其中的一部分
well we do have to take a quick quick
好吧， 我们必须迅速 采取行动
break when we come back as I mentioned
我们回来的 时候就像我提到的那样休息
we're going to be looking at episodic
我们将会 看一下 情节
DVD rips so stick around
DVD撕裂如此坚持
[Music]
[音乐]
whether you shop on ThinkGeek gearbest
你是否购买ThinkGeek gearbest
B&amp;H photo video eBay or Amazon or even
B＆H照片视频eBay或亚马逊甚至
if you want a free trial of audible
如果你想要免费试听听觉
you'll find the best deals and support
你会找到最好的交易 和支持
the shows we produce by simply visiting
我们通过简单访问制作的节目
the shopping sites you already frequents
您经常光顾的购物网站
by using the links on our website visit
通过使用我们网站上的链接 访问
category-five TV slash partners for the
五类电视斜线合作伙伴
full and ever-growing list and help us
完整且不断增长的清单并帮助我们
create more free content like this show
创建更多 像这个节目的 免费 内容
thank you for shopping with our partners
感谢您与我们的合作伙伴一起购物
and thank you for watching just before
并感谢你之前看
the break we had this cord up there and
我们 在那里 休息 了
we were even talking about discord I
我们甚至都在谈论 我 的不和谐
know but it was frozen didn't realize
知道，但它冻结没有 意识到
hopefully it's gonna work out a little
希望它能够解决 一些问题
better I mean it's it's just the
更好， 我的意思是它 只是它
positioning of the moon on this the
把 月亮定位在 这上面
first week of its a January of 2019 it
2019年1月的第一周它
is very close yeah exactly exactly so I
是非常接近是的， 所以我
think we've got everything going
我想我们已经把一切都 搞定了
somebody say something just to be sure
有人说些什么只是为了确定
drivers laughing this week we are going
司机笑了这周我们要去
to be kind of reproaching an old topic
有点谴责一个老话题
now on our YouTube channel there's a hot
现在在我们的 YouTube频道上 有一个热点
video about ripping copy-protected DVDs
关于翻录受版权保护的 DVD的视频
mm-hmm and this week we are going to be
mm-hmm，本周我们将会是
re addressing that because there are a
重新解决， 因为有一个
few questions that frequently come in on
经常出现的几个问题
that YouTube video hmm things around
该YouTube 视频的HMM 乾坤
essentially episode ik DVD rips okay now
基本上插曲ik DVD撕裂现在好了
when you rip a DVD if it's a movie it's
当你翻录DVD时，如果它是一部电影的话
pretty easy it's pretty straight forward
非常简单，非常直接
because it's one video and you're
因为这是一个视频而你是
ripping it and then coding it and and
抓住它然后编码它和
decoding it and and everything else but
解码它和其他一切但是
it's one video now when you get a DVD
当你拿到DVD时，它就是一个视频
set of your favorite shows it is a
你最喜欢的节目集是一个
little more challenging because
更具挑战性因为
typically each disc has multiple
通常每个光盘都有多个
episodes on it right so there is an
它上面就是剧集，所以有一个
added challenge to that so tonight we're
我们今晚增加了挑战
going to look at software that we have
去看看我们拥有的软件
looked at before but we're gonna take a
之前看过， 但 我们要拿一个
little bit of a different approach
一点点 不同的 方法
because we are going to be using an
因为我们将 要使用
episodic DVD set in order to do our reps
情节 DVD设置为了做我们的代表
okay then alright the process just so
好吧，那么好起来的过程 只是 如此
you know if you are interested only in
你知道你 是否 只 对此 感兴趣
ripping movies and not Episode ik DVDs
翻录电影而不是Episode ik DVD
the process is the same if you master
如果掌握 ，过程是一样的
this you will absolutely master the
这个你绝对会掌握的
ability to rip movies as well cuz as I
撷取电影， 以及 曲子，因为我的能力
say it's just one video on the disc
说这只是光盘上的一个视频
typically what the same process for an
通常什么 一个 相同的过程
episode of TV show worked the same as
电视节目的剧集也是 如此
say like DVD that's got special content
像 DVD 一样 有 特殊内容
yeah interviews and stuff absolutely
是的采访和绝对的东西
those are other videos on the discs yeah
这些 是 光盘 上的其他视频 是的
so quickly because I know one of the one
如此之快，因为我知道其中一个
of the comments on YouTube is I talk too
YouTube上的评论 也是我说的
much
许多
and so I want to just quickly mention
所以我想 快速提一下
that one of the reasons I would want to
这 是我想要的原因之一
do this and one of the reasons I want to
这样做是我想要的原因之一
do this has nothing to do with the
这与此无关
technology but it has to do with the
技术， 但它 与...有关
fact that I watch a lot of British shows
事实上， 我观看了很多 英国节目
so they come to me when I order them off
所以当 我下令 时 他们会来找 我
of Amazon UK they come to me region
亚马逊英国他们来到我的地区
coded to the UK so they don't play in a
编码到英国，所以他们不玩
local Canadian DVD player right so I
当地的加拿大DVD播放器， 所以我
have to rip it in order to be able to
要撕了， 为了 能够
watch it on my TV because its region
在我的电视上看它，因为它的地区
coated C and for me I like this because
涂 C和我，我喜欢这个， 因为
I have a ton of DVDs but we're looking
我 有 很多DVD，但我们正在 寻找
at getting a new sound system right that
获得一个 新的音响系统
they don't have DVD players yeah all of
他们没有DVD 播放器耶 所有 的
our TVs are connected to Plex so I want
我们的电视连接到Plex 所以我想要
to be able to watch exactly you you may
能够准确地 看到 你
have a blu-ray player which plays DVDs
有一个 播放 DVD 的蓝光播放器
as well but a lot of us have multimedia
同样， 但我们很多人都有 多媒体
centers and that's the other comment
中心， 这是另一个评论
that comes in on our youtube channel is
在我们的 youtube频道上出现的是
well why would I want to rip things to a
好吧，为什么我要把事情撕成碎片呢？
computer so that I can watch them on my
电脑让我可以 在我的电脑上观看 它们
laptop no this can these files can be
笔记本电脑 没有这个可以这些文件
watched on Smart TVs on set-top boxes on
在机顶盒 上的 智能电视上观看
I have a computer in my cellar that has
我的 酒窖里 有一台电脑
an HDMI cable coming out of it to the
一条HDMI线缆从它出来
back of a 55 inch TV and that's our
55 英寸电视的背面， 这是我们的
system so that's how we watch our TV
系统，这就是我们看电视的方式
from plex so I put them on my plex media
来自plex所以我把它们放在 我的plex媒体上
server and then we watch the shows up on
服务器，然后我们观看节目
our big-screen TV so this is not just so
我们的大屏幕电视所以不仅如此
you can watch it in a portable means of
你可以 用便携式的方式 观看 它
taking it with you on a laptop though
虽然在笔记本电脑上随身携带它
that is one good use case too if your
如果你的话 ，这也是一个很好的用例
kids are going away to school and they
孩子们要去学校和他们
have a bunch of DVDs they might not be
他们可能没有一堆DVD
able to take them all with them but you
除了你 ， 他们 能把 它们全部 带走
can rip them to their hard drive and
可以将它们撕裂自己的硬盘驱动器和
then all of a sudden they've
然后 他们 突然间
their entire library and are able to
他们的整个音乐库 ， 并能
take that to school with them just as an
采取到学校与他们一样 的
example for the record we're not
记录的例子我们不是
breaking any laws here tonight we own
我们今晚在这里 违反任何法律
the DVDs that we are ripping this is
我们正在翻录的DVD 是
about making your content that you
关于制作你的内容
already own more accessible on your
已经拥有 更多的可访问性
devices perfect I don't own a DVD player
设备完美我没有DVD 播放器
I think I own a DVD player but I think
我 想我拥有一台 DVD播放机， 但我想
it's somewhere in the garage it's not
它在车库的某个地方并非如此
connected to any of my devices
连接到我的任何 设备
especially with the advent of
特别是 随着它的到来
flat-screen TVs I no longer have a
平板电视我不再拥有
cabinet with DVD players and VCRs and
带DVD播放机 和录像机的机柜
things and I don't want to have it
事情，我不想拥有它
sitting on the floor below the TV that's
坐在电视机下面的地板上
mounted on the wall so it's just a
安装在墙上所以它只是一个
different world but I own the content
不同的世界，但 我拥有内容
and in fact this is a show that I bought
事实上这 是 我买的 一个节目
for my wife but technically for my wife
对于我的妻子，但技术上对我的妻子
and I to enjoy together inspector Lewis
和我一起享受督察刘易斯
it's a great murder mystery show if you
如果你这是一个伟大的谋杀神秘节目
haven't seen it from PBS and and it is
没有从 PBS 那里看到它 ，而且确实如此
what nine seasons on Oh 18 discs 18 DVDs
什么九季 哦18碟18张DVD
that's crazy right so this is something
这是疯了吧 ，所以这是 什么
that I want to be on my plex media
我希望成为我的plex媒体
server because I don't I don't have a
服务器，因为我不我没有
DVD player to put the DVDs in so why are
放DVD的 DVD 播放器为什么这样
we ripping DVDs and not blu-rays sighs
我们翻录DVD而不是蓝光 叹息
because notice I can compress them not
因为通知我可以不压缩它们
everything plays a blu-ray but if I rip
一切都播放蓝光， 但如果我撕裂
it to a file then it would fine right
它到一个文件然后它会很好
right it's it's a valid question and
对，这是一个有效的问题和
this is another one that you've been
这是 你 去过的 另一个
sending in the best answer I can give
发送 我能给出的最佳答案
you for that is let's just think about
你 是让我们 想想
the technology for just one moment now
这项技术现在只有一瞬间
blu-ray you would say is it's better
蓝光你会说它会更好
quality absolutely you can get 1080p
质量绝对可以获得1080p
blu-ray 4k blu-ray these are only 480p
蓝光4k蓝光这些只有480p
and granted they still look great but
并且 他们仍然看起来很棒但是
DVD is much less quality than blu-ray
DVD的质量远低于蓝光
that's why blu-ray is the you know the
这就是为什么蓝光是你所知道的
current optical standard anyways think
目前的光学标准反正认为
about your computer okay do you have a
关于你的电脑好吗，你有吗？
DVD drive on my computer right yeah you
我的电脑上的 DVD 驱动器是的你是的
do yep do you have a blu-ray drive no no
你有没有蓝光 驱动器 没有没有
mmm-hmm when you buy a computer even
mmm-hmm 当你 甚至 买电脑的时候
when you build a computer your computer
当你 构建一台 计算机时
has DVD capabilities right we may not
我们可能没有 DVD功能
necessarily use it to its full capacity
必须充分利用它
a lot of us use it you know sometimes to
很多我们使用它你有时会知道
burn discs and things like that but most
刻录光盘和类似的东西，但大多数
computers I don't want to be so general
电脑我不想这么一般
but majority of computers will not have
但大多数计算机都没有
blu-ray drives so you cannot rip blu-ray
蓝光驱动， 所以你不能撕裂 蓝光
on a DVD Drive you can rip DVD and every
在DVD驱动器上， 你可以翻录DVD和每一个
computer since years ago has DVD if it
计算机自几年前以来就有DVD了
has an optical drive right right there
右边有一个光驱
was CD then DVD in every computer has it
是CD然后DVD 在每台电脑都有它
blu-ray was never adopted as a computer
蓝光从未被 用作计算机
standard you can spend extra money you
标准你可以花额外的钱， 你
can buy extra devices to can to give
可以购买额外的设备给予
yourself blu-ray but I imagine that if
你自己是蓝光，但我想如果
you've done that you already know what
你已经完成了， 你已经知道了什么
you're doing and you've already know how
你正在做，你已经知道如何
to rip because why would you spend the
撕裂，因为你为什么要花钱
extra hundreds of dollars on an upgrade
升级额外数百美元
for your computer that when you don't
为你的电脑，当你不
even know what it does it's not so the
即使知道它做了 什么也不是这样
drive that is built into your computer
计算机 内置的驱动器
and in my laptop today is DVD that's all
在我的 笔记本电脑今天是DVD 这一切
it will read and then CD its downward
它将读取 然后 将 其向下CD
compatible but it will not do blu-ray so
兼容，但 它不会做蓝光
that's the answer to that and and the
这是这个问题的答案 ，并与
other point about that is that we're
关于 这 一点的另一点 是 ，我们是
doing this for free yes because I'm huge
这样做是免费的，因为我很大
I already have the hardware DVD drive in
我 已经有硬件 DVD驱动器了
my laptop I already have the well I'm
我的笔记本电脑我 已经很好了
gonna have the software in about five
将有大约五个软件
minutes I'm going to show you how to get
几分钟我 要告诉你如何获得
it it's absolutely free if I wanted to
如果我愿意 ，它绝对免费
rip blu-ray I have to invest in new
撕裂蓝光我必须投资新的
hardware I have to buy commercial
硬件我必须购买商业
software I have to go through all those
软件我必须经历所有这些
hoops so we're not going there it's all
篮球， 所以我们不会 去 那里
about the DVD all right so the product
关于DVD 没事所以产品
that we're gonna be using is called
我们将要使用的 是被称为
handbrake and I do have the capability
手刹和我确实有能力
of bringing this up on my screen so I'm
把它放在我的屏幕上所以我
just gonna do that for you let's go hand
只是要 为 你 做的 ，让我们携手
brake dot F R now this software is
刹车点FR现在这个软件是
available for Windows Mac and Linux and
适用于Windows Mac和Linux 和
it's absolutely free I'm gonna do the
它完全免费我会做的
demonstration on Windows 10 tonight so
今晚在Windows 10上进行演示
I've just clicked on the download button
我刚刚点击了下载按钮
and it asked me do I want to keep it and
它问我是否要 保留它
yes I want to keep that file so
是的，我想保留该文件
now it's downloading this 12 megabyte
现在它正在下载这个12兆字节
file it's gonna be here in 10 seconds
文件它会在10秒内到达
here we go megabytes so he's super tiny
这里我们去兆字节， 所以他超级小
so this is a program that's going to
所以这是 那将 一个程序
allow us to copy these DVDs to a file
允许我们将这些DVD复制到一个文件中
right so understand we're not making a
是的，所以明白我们没有做到
copy from a DVD to another DVD no right
从DVD复制到另一张DVD无权
we're we're taking the data off of the
我们正在把数据从中 获取
DVD we're going to remove the copy
DVD 我们要删除副本
protection and we're going to then
保护我们要 那么
encode it to a file format mp4 which is
将其编码为mp4的文件格式
going to allow us to watch it on our
允许 我们 在我们的 观看
set-top box on our plex media server all
我们的plex媒体服务器上的机顶盒全部
of those things ok so you said remove
那些东西好， 所以你说删除
the copy protection yes now do we
复制保护 现在是的我们
eventually put copy protection back on
最终重新启用了复制保护
okay so should most systems that have
好的，大多数系统都应该这样
DRM protection deep DRM DCA yeah DRM DRM
DRM保护深DRM DCA 是的DRM DRM
would they still recognize it without
如果没有，他们还能认出来吗？
the copy protection ok so understand
复制保护确定如此理解
Jeff we're not going to change the DVD
杰夫， 我们不会改变DVD
correct okay yeah DVDs are a read-only
正确 没关系是的DVD是只读的
medium right DVD RW that's different
中右DVD RW不同
that means rewrite right but when you
这意味着重写 正确，但当你
buy a commercial DVD video set it is
买它是商业DVD视频集
write read-only right
写 只读 权
they've silk-screened it and pressed it
他们用丝网印刷并按下它
so we're not making any changes that are
所以我们 没有 做任何 改变
going to affect that disc it's going to
会影响到它的光盘
still work exactly the same it's going
仍然可以工作 它会 完全 一样
to have the same copy protection what
有什么相同的版权保护
we're doing is when we copy it to the
我们正在做的是当我们将它复制到
hard drive of my computer we're going to
我们要去的电脑 硬盘
remove the the protection which will
删除将要保护的
obfuscate the video ok because if I just
混淆视频 确定，因为如果我 只是
simply if I just put a DVD in my drive
只是我只是把DVD放在我的驱动器中
and copied all the files to my computer
并将所有文件复制到我的电脑
and tried to play the VOB files they'd
并尝试播放 他们 的 VOB文件
be green lines yes and it would be all
是绿线是的，这将是全部
messed up because there's copy
搞砸了， 因为有副本
protection that prevents me from making
保护，阻止我 做
that copy right and rightly so
这是正确和正确的复制
I go back to the fact that I own these
我回到 我拥有这些的事实
discs I'm not showing you how to bootleg
光盘我没有告诉你如何盗版
or how to make illegal copies go do that
或者如何制作非法复制品
what we're doing here is is just making
我们在这里做的只是制作
this for ourselves so with that file now
这对我们自己来说，现在 用 这个文件
download it I hope that answers your
下载它我希望能回答你的问题
question does ok so there's a handbrake
问题确实没问题， 所以有一个手刹
now ready to install so I'm gonna click
现在准备安装所以我要 点击
on that
在那
and we're going to install that next I
然后我们将安装 下一个
agree and
同意和
next perfect now you think you're done
下一个完美的现在你认为 你已经完成了
but you're not I mentioned about
但你不是我提到过的
copy-protection yes okay right hand
复制保护是 好的 右手
brake is free software and they need to
刹车 是免费的软件 ，他们需要
be careful that they are not
小心他们不是
distributing software that can be used
分发可以 使用的 软件
for illegal purposes okay right so right
用于非法目的 好吗 权这样的权利
now in its current state I can rip my
现在处于目前的状态，我可以撕掉我的
family movies I can rip my wedding DVD
家庭电影我可以撕开我的婚礼DVD
that was created for me but I cannot rip
这是为我创造的，但我不能撕裂
commercial DVDs with copy protection I
商业DVD与复制保护 我
have to go one step further in order to
必须更进一步 才能
rip and decode the copy protection
翻录并解码复制保护
remove that and that's using a tool from
删除那个，那是使用工具
VLC which we all know and love yeah VLC
VLC ，我们都知道和爱 是的VLC
the video player it's able to play
它能够播放的视频播放器
everything and we can use some of their
一切，我们可以使用他们的一些
technology in order to bypass and get
技术，以绕过和获得
around the copy protection meats so it's
复制保护 肉周围所以它是
a little hard to find when I go to VLC .
我去VLC时有点难找 。
is it org nope VLC let's just know now
是吧org nope VLC让我们现在才知道
it's in my memory VLC . no video lan org
它在我的记忆VLC中。 没有视频局 组织
that's how they always get me ok video
这就是他们总是让我 确定 视频
land or in projects you see lib DVD CSS
土地或项目你看到DVD DVD CSS
and gives you all these now live DVD CSS
并为您提供所有这些现在直播的DVD CSS
is specifically a library designed for
特别是为...设计的库
accessing dvds like a block device
像块设备一样访问dvds
without having to bother about the
无需 担心
decryption it's a fancy way to say this
解密它是一种奇特的说法
gets around
到处走走
the encoding that protects the DVD you
保护DVD的编码方式
can go into releases and you go into
可以进入发布，你进入
1.2.12 and then you see win 64 see all
1.2.12 然后你看到胜利64看到所有
the hoops that you got to go through
你得去通过箍
know why that version did they
知道为什么那个版本 做了他们
discontinued it after they stopped
他们停下 来 后停止了
making it for they stopped compiling it
因为他们停止编译它
for windows ok so that particular
对于Windows确定如此特别
version 1.2.12 anyway so you're on
无论如何版本1.2.12 所以你在
windows let's make it simple I've
Windows让我们变得简单
created a hot link for you all you have
创建一个热链接，你所有你 有
to do is go cat 5 dot TV /lib DVD CSS
要做的就是去猫 5点电视 / lib DVD CSS
forget about the DLL because it's just a
忘了 DLL，因为它只是 一个
hot link when I click on that enter it's
热门链接， 当我点击 它 输入它
going to redirect to the file and it's
要重定向 到文件，它是
going to allow me to download it
要 允许我 下载
keep what's it again lit cat5 dot TV
保持 它再次点亮cat5 点电视
/lib Scott DVD Z s s Lib DVD CSS and you
/ lib Scott DVD Z ss Lib DVD CSS和你
see that below as well so now I've
看下面也是如此，所以现在我
downloaded that file just save it to
下载该文件只是保存到
your downloads folder I cannot reiterate
你的下载文件夹我不能重申
enough you do not save this to its final
你不能 把它 保存 到最后
destination your Windows system won't
你的Windows 系统 目的地 不会
allow you to do that and it will end up
允许你这样做，它会结束
saving it in the wrong spot and then
把它保存在错误的地方 然后
your decoding will not work okay okay I
你的解码将无法正常工作 好吧 我
need to now take that dll file which has
现在需要拿那个 有的dll文件
been downloaded to my downloads folder
已下载 到我的下载文件夹
and I actually downloaded it twice so
我实际上下载了两次
it's got a one after it I want the the
它之后有一个我想要 的
original DLL file so I just want to copy
原始的DLL文件， 所以我只想复制
that file Lib DVD CSS - to DLL is what
那个文件 Lib DVD CSS  - 到DLL是什么
it's calling it right now and I'm going
它正在调用它，我 要去了
to go now again I'm on Windows this will
现在再次声明，我 去 在Windows上会
work on Mac and Linux it's just that the
在Mac和Linux上工作就是这样的
file locations are different find where
文件位置不同找到哪里
handbrake installed - and you'll be able
安装了手刹- 你将能够
to do this on Windows it's usually going
要在Windows上执行此操作，通常会这样做
to be in your C Drive in Program Files
在程序文件中的C盘中
and then a folder now called handbrake
然后是一个名为handbrake的文件夹
because remember I installed a program
因为记得 我安装了一个程序
called handbrake so here it is but it's
叫做手刹，所以在这里，但它是
missing the DLL to decode that so I'm
错过了DLL解码，所以我
going to right click and hit paste and
要右击 ， 打糊
here's the warning you're gonna need
这是你需要的警告
administrator permission to do this
管理员权限执行此操作
continue so now in that folder along
所以现在继续该 文件夹 中 沿
with my handbrake dot exe is also live
用我的手刹点exe 也是活的
DVD CSS - - DLL that is a necessary step
DVD CSS  - -  DLL是必要的 一步
if you're getting garbled video on your
如果你的 视频出现乱码
rips you've you've done that incorrectly
撕裂你，你已经做错 了
okay
好的
download it to your downloads folder
将其下载到您的下载文件夹
then copy it or cut it and paste it into
然后将其复制 或剪切并粘贴到其中
the same folder as handbrake Exe do not
同一文件夹 手刹埃克 不
open the program before that point okay
在那之前打开程序好吧
notice the the steps that we've taken
注意我们采取的步骤
now I can close this and I'm gonna bring
现在我可以关闭它，我会带来的
up handbrake on my screen and I've
手刹了我的屏幕上， 我已经
already inserted the first disc of the
已插入的第一张光盘
set okay
好的
do that first put your disc in if you
如果你这样做，首先 把 你的光盘 放进去
bring up handbrake first and then put
首先提起手刹然后再放
the disc in you're probably not going to
你的光盘可能不会
see your your desk okay I put it in
看到你的桌子好吧我把 它 放进 去了
first okay now I'm gonna bring up
第一个好，现在我要提起 来
handbrake
手刹
here it comes and you see now it has
它来了，你现在看到了它
detected the DVD so hit OK or just click
检测到DVD 所以点击 确定或只是点击
on that DVD and now it's scanning the
在那张DVD上 现在正在扫描
titles of this disc now on the box set
这个光盘的标题现在在盒子上
here there's a couple of things so on
这里有 几 件事情如此
the back of the disc on the case right
案件右侧 的光盘背面
disc one okay and then there's the pilot
光盘一个没关系，然后是飞行员
and series pilot and whom the gods would
和系列飞行员 ，众神会
destroy 2 episode 2 episode 1 disc 2
摧毁2集第2集第1集光盘 2
episodes so on that disc now I can see
现在我可以看到那张光盘 上的剧集
if I look under title
如果我看下标题
I see three files well what what on
我看到三个文件很好
earth right observe one hour 37 minutes
大地观察一小时37分钟
and four seconds one hour 38 minutes and
和4秒 1小时38分钟
38 seconds one minute 39 seconds that's
这是38秒1分39秒
the episode yeah so the first two files
这一集是啊所以前 两个文件
are the first two titles that it sees on
是前两个冠军，它认为 在
the DVD those are the episodes and then
那些DVD是那些剧集然后
this is probably the menu it's like a
这可能就像菜单一样
one-minute loop so I'm going to first
一分钟的循环，所以我 要先
click on the first one and up here see
点击第一个，在这里看
this here this is extremely important I
这在这里 这 是极其重要的 我
need to observe how they created this
需要 观察他们是如何创造了这个
DVD the encoding that they used so this
DVD 他们使用的编码就是这样
is 720 by 480 but it is actually
是720乘480但实际上是
anamorphic so it's 853 by 480 is the
变形所以它是853乘480是
actual resolution of the disc and this
光盘的实际分辨率和这个
is key the framerate 23.9 8 frames per
关键 帧率为每帧23.9 8帧
second keep that in the back of your
第二， 保持在 你 的后面
mind
心神
so I want to you notice that it
所以我想让你注意到它
defaulted too fast
违约太快了
1080p 30 yep don't want that okay
1080p 30 是的，不要那么好
because a DVD is only 480p
因为DVD只有480p
why would I rip it in 1080p which will
为什么我 会用 1080p 撕掉 它
upscale it will create a 1080p file but
高档它会创建一个1080p文件但是
the source is only 480p so I'm basically
来源只有480p，所以我基本上
just stretching it out it would just
只是 将它 伸展出去
make a bigger file yeah uselessly yeah
做一个更大的档案是的无用是的
so what I want to do is I want to as
所以我想要做的就是我要 为
closely as possible match my encoders to
使之尽量接近我的编码器
the DVD itself that's why the framerate
DVD 本身就是 帧率 的原因
is very very important so the first
非常重要所以第一个
thing I'm going to do with the DVD is
我打算用DVD做的事情是
I'm going to change my preset to general
我要将 我的预设 更改 为一般
fast 480p 30 because that's the closest
快480p 30因为 那是最接近的
thing to match a DVD 480p
匹配DVD 480p的东西
30 seconds 30 frames per second so next
30秒30 帧/秒，接下来
thing I want to do is turn on web
我想要做的就是打开网络
optimized what that will do Jeff is that
优化杰夫的目标是什么
will help so that your plex media server
将帮助您的plex媒体服务器
if you pause it it can resume easier ok
如果你暂停它可以恢复更容易
skim you can skim easier because it's in
脱脂你可以更容易地浏览，因为它在
your web browser when you're using plex
您使用plex时的Web浏览器
so that helps web optimized is important
这样有助于 网络优化 很重要
dimensions I just want to bring you back
尺寸我只是想带你回来
to this we don't need to change anything
对此我们不需要改变任何东西
it's already detected 720 by 480
它 已经由480检测720
anamorphic is set to automatic and you
变形设置为自动和你
see that the display size is coming out
看到显示尺寸即将出现
to 853 by 480 which matches 853 by 480
到853乘480，匹配853乘480
the actual disk that I've inserted okay
我插入的实际磁盘 没问题
next up I just want to show you filters
接下来我只想向您展示过滤器
we have deinterlacing this is all just
我们已经去隔行扫描这一切都是公正的
left default but what that does because
保留默认但这是因为
our computers are devices or
我们的电脑是 设备或
progressive-scan
逐行扫描
so each frame is a full frame interlaced
所以每帧都是 隔行扫描的全帧
the DVD is actually interlaced so it's
DVD实际上是交错的， 所以它是
only half of the frame per frame so so
每帧只有一半帧，所以
deinterlacing is going to fix the lines
去隔行将修复线条
that you see in some videos if you
如果你 在某些视频中 看到的 话
didn't have the interlace and you'd have
没有隔行扫描而且你有
lines through everything especially
特别是通过一切
during action shots so just leave those
在拍摄动作期间，请离开那些
leave those filters as they are because
保留那些过滤器， 因为它们
they're the defaults are perfect we do
他们的默认设置是完美的
not need to I don't even know how to say
不需要我甚至不知道怎么说
it details
它的细节
assign because this is if we were
分配，因为如果我们是
upscaling to 30 frames per second but we
升级到每秒30帧，但 我们
want to actually match the 23.9 a so
想要真正匹配23.9一个
just forget about filters I just wanted
忘记我想要的过滤器
to show you that ok leave everything the
告诉你 ，确保 把一切都留下来
same as it is except we want to set a
除了我们想设置一个之外 ，它 是 一样 的
constant frame rate because we know that
恒定帧率因为我们知道
it is twenty three point nine eight
这是 二十三点九八
frames per second the default is thirty
每秒帧数默认为30
frames per second I actually want to
我实际想要的 每秒帧数
match the DVD so keep in mind I am not
匹配DVD所以请 记住我不是
telling you to set this to twenty three
告诉你把它设置为二十三
point nine eight frames per second or it
每秒9点八帧或 它
which is really 23.976 that's the
这实在 是 23.976 这就是
correct option for this particular disc
此特定光盘的正确选项
but every time you insert a disc you
但每次 你插入 光盘你
need to observe those top stats so that
需要观察那些最佳统计数据
you know what that disc is the next disc
你知道， 光盘是什么盘 下
that I put on in even if it's from the
我穿上的，即使是来自
same set might be thirty frames per
同一组可能是 每 帧30帧
second
第二
for sure yeah yeah and it does happen
肯定是啊是的，确实发生了
and in fact with this particular DVD set
事实上， 这个特殊的DVD套装
once you get to the second second set of
一旦你到了第二第二套
disks it goes up to 30 frames per second
磁盘 它上升到 每秒 30帧
that could be because they were shooting
那可能是因为他们在 射击
in 24 frames per second and then they
每秒 24 帧， 然后他们
switched to 30 P for NTSC something like
对于NTSC，切换到30 P 就像
that
那
I've just observed that so I'm not
我刚刚观察到，所以我不是
saying to do this at 23.976 generically
说要 一般在23.976 这样做
I'm saying observe what the disk is and
我说要观察 磁盘是 什么 和
match that so I'm creating a copy of
匹配， 所以我正在创建一个副本
this that is so close to the original
这是如此接近 原始
that you're probably not going to notice
你可能不会注意到
the difference so everything else
差别 所以其他一切
so remember constant framerate 23.976
所以记住恒定 帧率 23.976
matches 23 point 9 8 which is a rounded
匹配23 点 9 8 这 是一个圆形
number you may have 30 frames per second
您可以拥有每秒30帧的 数字
or 29.97 on different disks but this
或29.97在不同的磁盘上， 但这
disk is that
磁盘就是 这样
[Music]
[音乐]
for a limited time get your hands on
在有限的时间内开始
limited-edition shirts from the category
这类限量版衬衫
5 TV network these high quality shirts
5电视网这些高品质的衬衫
are manufactured by teespring
由 teespring制造
a fundraising website and your purchase
筹款网站和您的购买
will help support the shows we produce
将有助于支持我们 制作 的节目
get yours today and send us your
今天送你的，送我们你的
pictures to be featured on the
图片将在上面展出
corresponding show visit cap 5 dot TV
相应的节目访问帽5点电视
slash shirts to support us and get your
削减衬衫， 以支持我们，让你的
official Network shirt today cap five
官方网络衬衫今日上限 五
dot TV slash shirts now if you I mean
如果你的 意思， 现在点电视斜杠衬衫
chances are you're not gonna find that
你不可能找到那个机会
your disc is different but then those
你的光盘是不同的，但那些
numbers but if you do find this
数字， 但如果你找到这个
different are you better to downscale to
不同的是你最好缩减到
the clothes closest lower or closest
最接近或最接近的衣服
higher DVDs generally are going to be 24
更高的DVD通常是24
frames a second right 30 frames a second
每秒30帧，第二帧
29.97 frames a second you know you're
你知道自己每秒29.97帧
not gonna have four frame a second DVDs
不会有四帧第二张DVD
or that's a 6,000 yeah there there are
或者这是一个 6000啊 有有
standards right and so these these
标准是正确的，所以这些
represent the standards and then some
代表标准，然后一些
like that here 60 frames a second 120
像这样60帧每秒120
frames a second 59.94 yeah and it will
一秒钟59.94 是的，它会
show you here what the frames per second
在这里向您展示每秒的帧数
is that's what we want to match up audio
这就是我们想要匹配的音频
I'm just gonna leave it as is oh and
我只是要把它留下来哦哦
back here constant quality I'm gonna
回到这里我会保持不变的质量
leave at 20 if you increase that it's
如果增加 它就离开20
gonna the numbers gonna go down and
数字会下降而且
you're just gonna get a bigger file size
你只是 要 获得更大的文件大小
but I think 20 is a pretty happy place
但我认为20岁是一个非常幸福的地方
you're gonna get really good quality
你会得到非常好的 品质
without going over the top as far as
但不超过 上 尽可能
file size goes audio I'm just going to
文件大小去音频我只是要
leave as is but if there are other audio
保持原样，但如果有其他音频
tracks you can select them if you want
您可以 根据需要 选择 它们
to choose a different language for
为...选择不同的 语言
example I'm just using the English and
例如，我只是使用英语和
that's all that there is on this DVD if
这 就是这张DVD 的全部内容
it has Italian and you would prefer the
它有意大利语，你更喜欢
Italian track you can actually change
意大利赛道你实际上可以改变
that and that's what will be ripped you
那 就是扯掉你的东西
can include both if there are multiple
如果有多个，可以包括两者
tracks you can also include those and
跟踪你还可以包括 那些和
then you can change it using VLC or your
然后你可以使用 VLC或 你的 更改它
player that's a cool option yeah
玩家，这是一个很酷的选择是的
absolutely everything else is just gonna
绝对一切都会如此
stay as is those are the key things so
保持原样那些是关键的事情
now save as I'm just gonna browse
现在保存，我 只是要浏览
somewhere on my computer go on to my
在我的电脑上的某个地方继续我的
desktop the naming is important
桌面命名很重要
especially if you're using plex media
特别是如果你正在使用plex媒体
server or some other kind of media
服务器或其他一些媒体
server you've got to start with season
服务器你必须从 赛季 开始
number and the episode number so s01e01
号码和剧集号码如此s01e01
is the beginning of this file because
是这个文件的开头因为
otherwise it's not going to show up on
否则它不会出现
your plex media server so I'm gonna call
你的plex媒体服务器，所以我打电话
this s 0 0 1 0 1 and then I do a hyphen
这个 s 0 0 1 0 1然后 我做了一个 连字符
and then I'm gonna call this series
然后我会 打电话给这个系列
pilot because that's actually what they
飞行员，因为这 实际上是他们的
call it dot mp4 don't forget to specify
叫它点mp4别忘了指定
that save now I'm not actually doing
现在保存，我 实际上并 没有 这样做
anything yet what I
我还有什么
I want to add that to my queue now if I
如果我 ，我 现在想把它添加到我的 队列中
look at the queue we can see it's there
看看队列我们可以看到它在那里
it's ready to go but I this is episode
它准备好了， 但我这是插曲
ik remember so now if I was just doing a
我现在记得，如果我只是做一个
diva movie I'm done right I could just
女主角的电影，我做 对 了 我可以 只
rip it and I'm done but because this is
撕掉它，我已经完成但因为这是
episode ik and there are two episodes on
剧集ik并且有两集
this desk next step is to now pull down
这个桌子下一步 是现在拉 下来
the title and change to the next one
标题并改为 下 一个
episode two and I'm gonna leave
第二集 ，我 不会 离开
everything as is it's already using the
一切都是因为它 已经在使用了
same settings that I already set but now
我已 设置的相同设置但现在
I don't need to browse I'm just going to
我不需要浏览我只是去
delete the last the automated file name
删除最后一个自动化的 文件名
here and call it s01e02 and the episode
在这里，并 称之为s01e02 和剧集
number of or the episode name of number
号码的编号或剧集名称
two for this show is called
这个节目的两个 叫做
whom the gods would destroy and so back
众神会摧毁谁，所以回来
at hand break I'm just gonna put that in
手头休息我只是想把它放进去
there or I could type it dot mp4 now add
那里或我可以输入点mp4现在 添加
to my queue so the specifications would
到我的队列 所以规格会
never change episodes episode on the
永远不会改变剧集的剧集
same disk it would just be disk to disk
相同的磁盘它只是磁盘到磁盘
it might change the disk itself is a
它可能会改变磁盘本身就是一个
certain frame rate is the certain yeah
某些帧速率是一定的 耶
resolution but and the next disk might
分辨率，但下一个磁盘可能
be a different frame rate right yeah I
是一个不同的帧速率是的我
haven't seen it mixed it could
没有看到它混合它可以
technically I think it could be mixed
从技术上讲，我认为 它可能 是混合的
okay but I've never seen it I just feel
好吧，但我从来没有见过它，我只 觉得
like perhaps you'd get lulled into it
也许 你会被哄骗
say there was like seven episodes on a
说有一集七集
disk yeah lulled into repeating and
磁盘是的哄骗重复和
repeating that you put in a new desk and
重复你放入一张新桌子
well everything's changed yes watch that
好吧一切都改变了是看那个
yeah and you see how quick it is to
是的， 你看到它有多快
change it anyways and modify those
无论如何改变它 并修改它们
settings now if I look at my cue I have
如果我看看 我的提示，现在设置
both of those episodes in my cue all I
我所提到的这两集都是我的
need to do is hit start cue and pour
需要做的就是点击开始提示并倒入
yourself a coffee go sit down it's on my
自己 坐下来喝 咖啡 吧
i7 laptop this is gonna take about an
i7笔记本电脑这将需要一个
hour per episode so so close to
每集一小时如此接近
real-time because I don't know I don't
实时因为我 不 知道 我 没有
know that it's really that specific it's
知道它 确实是特定的
just that's how long it takes because
只是这需要多长时间，因为
what it's doing is its decoding removing
它正在做的是解码 删除
the copy protection or copying the file
复制 保护 或复制文件
itself and then encoding to the mp4
本身然后编码到mp4
format that matches the specifications
符合规范的格式
that I've given right so then I end up
我给了你的权利然后我结束了
with an mp4 file because this is going
用mp4文件，因为这样
to take two hours just before
前 两个小时
the show I actually set it up and did
节目其实我设置它，并 做了
exactly this and so I already have these
正是这样 ，所以我已经有了这些
two episodes ripped and that's why the
两集撕裂，这就是为什么
disc was already in my drive I'm just
光盘已经在我的驱动器中我只是
gonna close out of this and if I bring
如果我带来的话，我会关闭它
up my folder here where I ripped it you
我的文件夹在这里，我把它撕成碎片
can see now I've got these two files and
现在可以看到我有这两个文件和
if I click on it on my computer there it
如果我在电脑上点击它就可以了
is it's a perfect rip it looks fantastic
这是一个完美的裂缝它看起来 很棒
it looks perfect and up on my up on my
它看起来很完美而且依靠我
big-screen TV it looks wonderful
大屏幕 电视看起来很 精彩
cool and there you go so that is decoded
很酷，你去那里解码
and it works and we're good to go I like
和它的作品，我们是好去 ，我喜欢
this I have a drawer full of DVDs in art
我有一个装满 艺术DVD 的抽屉
and their unit yeah that I could spend
和他们的单位是的，我可以花
days ripping and we would love to show
撕裂的日子，我们很乐意展示
these things but we don't have a DVD
这些东西， 但 我们 没有 DVD
player anymore yeah so they're just kind
玩家了， 是的，所以 他们只是善良
of sit there we keep talking about all
坐在那里 我们一直在谈论所有
should we have just sold them off but
我们应该把它们卖掉但是
now it's like no there's a purpose you
现在就好像没有 你 的目的
can rip them and put them on your plex
可以撕开它们并将 它们放在你的plex上
media server yeah yeah and it's
媒体服务器是啊是的， 它是
absolutely like cuz the the video is
绝对喜欢这个视频
great the video looks even on my 55 inch
很棒的视频看起来甚至在我的55英寸
TV the 480p looks fabulous and because
电视480p 看起来很棒，因为
I've set the settings as I have the
我已经按照我的设置设置了设置
quality is stellar like there's no there
质量很棒，就像那里没有
no artifacting there's no there's no
没有神器，没有没有
perceptible loss it looks great
可感知的损失看起来很棒
it looks absolutely perfect so I think
它看起来绝对完美， 所以我想
that that covers everything that we need
那涵盖了我们需要的一切
to cover for this feature I hope that
为了 这个功能，我希望如此
you've enjoyed it and learned from it
您喜欢它，并从中 学到了
and I hope that it helps you to be able
我 希望 它能 帮助 你
to move your DVD library into your
将您的DVD 库 移动 到您的
current setup because I just don't have
目前的设置因为 我没有
the setup to play these anymore but I
除了我之外，还有设置来 播放这些
still buy them I still support the the
仍然买他们我仍然 支持
industries that make them and and and
制造它们的行业和和
I'm happy to do that and by doing that
我很高兴这样 做 ，并做到 这一点
I'm paying for it I bought these off of
我付了钱 ， 我买了 这些
Amazon right I'm not downloading illegal
亚马逊权利我没有下载非法
copies of videos I'm not breaking the
视频副本我没有打破
law I'm not stealing from the content
法律我不是在偷窃 内容
creators and but I still have the same
创作者，但我仍然有相同的
effect of being able to put it on my
能够把它 放在我身上的效果
devices and being able to put it on my
设备，并能够把它 放在 我的
plex media server or whatever other
plex媒体服务器或其他任何
device that I own that gives me access
我拥有的设备让我可以访问
to that content in a modern kind of way
以现代的方式来看那些内容
very cool there's a question from Seoul
很酷， 首尔 有一个问题
in the chatroom
在 聊天室
what if one just wants to rip without
如果只是想撕不什么
changing the encoding so DVD encoding is
改变编码所以DVD编码是
mpeg-2 right now but keep in mind it has
mpeg-2现在但请记住它 有
copy protection yes so you will not be
版权保护是这样你就 不会
able to play those files if you don't go
如果你不去，可以播放这些文件
through the process so part of this is
通过这个过程，所以这部分是
decoding then re encoding to a format
解码然后重新编码为格式
that your devices will be able to play
您的设备将 能够 播放
right that's the key thing so I hope
对，这是我希望的关键
that answers for you I hope that all of
那个答案对你来说我希望所有 的
your questions have been answered if you
你的问题已经回答了 ，如果你
have any more please comment below we
我们还有以下评论
got to jump over to the newsroom all
所有人都 跳到 新闻编辑室
right all right here are the stories
这就是故事
were covering this week in the category
本周在该类别中 进行了 报道
5 TV newsroom several US newspapers
5家电视新闻室 几家 美国报纸
suffered major printing and delivery
遭受重大印刷和交付
disruptions on Saturday following a
星期六之后中断了
cyber attack India will ban ecommerce
网络攻击印度将禁止电子商务
companies such as Amazon and Walmart
亚马逊和沃尔玛等公司
owned Flipkart from selling products in
拥有Flipkart 从销售产品
from companies in which they have an
来自他们拥有的公司
equity interest the first autonomous
股权是第一个自治的
freight train network is fully
货运列车网络是完整的
operational and Elon Musk claims to be
操作和埃隆马斯克 声称 是
on track for a 2026 Mars colony mission
轨道上的 2026火星殖民地使命
and reveals who will be on board the
并揭示谁是船上
first trips these stories are coming
第一次旅行这些故事 即将来临
right up don't go anywhere
没有 去任何地方
this is the category 5 TV newsroom
这是5类电视 新闻室
covering the week's top
覆盖本周的顶部
Linux bias Jeff Westen Jemma you're
Linux 偏见Jeff Westen Jemma你是
building a brand-new beautiful website
建立一个全新的美丽网站
what
什么
aren't you your terrible actor what this
你这不是你可怕的演员吗？
where acting comes into play I don't
代理发挥作用 我 不这样做
know you're supposed to act okay I'm
知道你 应该 行动 好 我是
building a really cool website are you
建立一个非常 酷的 网站 是你
building a really cool website just
建立一个非常酷的网站
because Jeff is confused doesn't mean
因为杰夫很困惑 并不 代表
you have to be visit cap five dot TV
你必须访问五点电视帽
slash dream host to sign up for
签名 梦想主持人 报名 参加
unlimited web hosting for your website
为您的网站无限制的虚拟 主机
with unlimited email accounts MySQL
无限的电子邮件 帐户 MySQL
databases the latest version of PHP
数据库最新版本的PHP
WordPress and more and even a free
WordPress和更多，甚至 是免费的
domain name registration it's less than
域名注册少于
six dollars per month so sign up today
每月 6美元，所以 今天 报名
cat five dot TV slash dream host just
猫 五点电视斜线梦想主持人刚刚
quickly before we get into it I heard
在 我们进入它 之前很快我听到了
that breath just want to let you all
那种气息只是想让 你们 所有人
know that some of the news stories were
知道一些 新闻报道
submitted this week by Roy W Nash we
本周由Roy W Nash提交我们
hear that he has been doing well and and
听说他一直表现不错
it's so great to receive some emails
收到一些电子邮件真是太棒了
from him this week and we look forward
本周来自他，我们期待着
to updates there but just thought I'd
在那里更新，但只是想我
give you a quick update so Thank You Roy
给你一个 快速更新，谢谢你罗伊
and here's the speedy health and a
这是快速的健康和一个
wonderful 2019 I'm Sasha Rickman and
精彩的2019年我是Sasha Rickman和
here are the top stories were following
以下是最热门的故事
this week several US newspapers suffered
本周几家美国报纸受到了影响
major printing and delivery disruptions
主要的印刷和交付中断
on Saturday following a cyber attack the
周六发生网络攻击后
attack led to delayed distribution of
攻击导致分发延迟
the Los Angeles Times Chicago Tribune
洛杉矶时报“芝加哥 论坛报”
Baltimore Sun and other titles belonging
巴尔的摩太阳和其他头衔 属于
to Tribune publishing the company said
据Tribune发布该公司称
it first detected the malware on Friday
它 在周五 首次发现 恶意软件
which hit papers sharing the same
哪篇文章分享了同样的文章
printing plant the LA Times said the
洛杉矶时报的印刷厂说
attack is believed to have come from
据信攻击 来自
outside the US an anonymous source with
美国以外的匿名消息来源
knowledge of the attack told the LA
对袭击的了解告诉了洛杉矶
Times we believe the intention of the
时代我们相信的意图
attack was to disable infrastructure
攻击是禁用基础设施
more specifically servers as opposed to
更具体地说，服务器而不是
looking to steal information westcoast
希望窃取信息westcoast
editions of The Wall Street Journal and
“华尔街日报”和“华尔街日报”
New York Times which share the same
纽约时报也有同样的看法
production platform in Los Angeles were
洛杉矶的生产平台
also affected the virus heard back
还听到了回复的病毒
office systems used to publish and
办公系统用于发布和
produce the newspapers another
再生产报纸
publication the Fort Lauderdale Sun
出版劳德 代尔堡太阳报
Sentinel was also crippled this weekend
哨兵本周末也瘫痪了
by a computer virus that shut down
通过 关闭计算机病毒
production and hampered
生产和阻碍
according to a story on its website a
根据其网站上的一个故事a
department of homeland security
国土安全部
officials said in a statement we are
官员们在一份声明中表示我们是
aware of reports of a potential cyber
了解潜在网络的报道
incident affecting several news outlets
影响几个新闻媒体的事件
and are working with our government and
并 正在与 我们的政府和
industry partners to better understand
行业合作伙伴 更好地了解
the situation investigators at the
调查人员的情况
Federal Bureau of Investigations were
联邦调查局是
not immediately available for comment
没有立即 发表评论
okay so that's scary because so begins
好的，所以这很可怕，因为这样开始
the year yeah you can get in to the news
今年是的，你可以得到新闻
I'm eager to hear more about how the
我很想听到更多关于如何
attack occurred mm-hmm but yeah I mean
攻击发生了mm-hmm，但是我的 意思是
that can what do you say to that
那你能怎么说呢？
that we have such a digital connected I
我们有这样的数字连接我
think about newspapers and think about
想想报纸和思考
how old-school the technology of a
怎么老派的技术了
newspaper is and yet they are reliant
报纸是，但他们依赖
now as much as we are on the technology
现在就像 我们都在 技术
that's internet connected and everything
这是互联网连接和一切
else so there's so many news stations
否则就有这么多新闻台
whether it be TV paper whatever they
无论是电视纸还是电视纸
have remote correspondence that in a lot
有很多远程通信
of cases probably right into a network
案件可能 正好 进入网络
yeah and so if their network is
是的，如果他们的网络是
regularly getting data traffic coming in
定期获取数据流量
from outside the network I mean you've
从网络外部我的意思是你
got a lot of holes that you need to have
得到了很多 洞 ， 你需要有
protected and if they are connected
保护，如果他们连接
stations say through a network you know
电台通过你知道的网络说
you hit one you could potentially hit
你打了一个你可能会 命中的人
them all I mean so often they share
他们所有我的意思是他们经常分享
content and it's like where is that
内容和它就像在哪里
vulnerability mm-hmm but at the same
漏洞mm-hmm 但 同样如此
time I just kind of go well it's another
时间我有点好， 这是另一回事
story
故事
move it on I'm gonna have my coffee well
移动它，我要去有我的咖啡 以及
yeah a little bit but it kind of speaks
是啊一点点 ，但它那种说话
to the the infrastructure issues that
对基础设施 问题
companies have to like these are and
公司必须喜欢这些和
these are big companies but these are
这些都是大公司， 但这些都是
old companies yes so you know as the
老公司是的， 所以你知道 的
infrastructure progressed along with the
基础设施与...一起发展
technology has the security measures
技术有安全措施
that are in place progressed along with
随着 时间的 推移 到位
that technology so we have to look at
这项技术让我们不得不看
you know as as you know maybe the
你知道就像你知道的那样
businesses that we work at grow and
我们工作 的企业成长和
evolve into today you know are the
进化到今天，你知道的是
technologies that are in place to
技术， 是到位
protect
保护
that's against cyberattack are they up
他们起来反对网络攻击
to snuff I still feel like a lot of
鼻烟 我还是 觉得很多
times it's somebody who's just not
有些人 不是
security conscious it could be one user
安全意识到 它可能是一个用户
on the network that clicked on a file in
在点击文件的网络上
an email right who knows right I think
一个电子邮件权利谁知道我认为正确
of those cities that we've heard of in
我们听说过 在这些城市的
the past we've heard on the news where
过去 我们 在新闻中听说过
suddenly all of their city computers get
突然 他们 所有的 城市 电脑都得到了
the old pay the Bitcoin because we've
旧的支付比特币因为我们已经
ransomware is your computer it's like
勒索软件 是 你的电脑就好像
yeah alter goes one person you know who
是的， 改变一个你 认识的人
just works
只是工作
yeah it's true you know it's scary
是的，你知道它是 可怕的
because you really you don't know what
因为 你真的 不 知道是什么
causes something like that and like you
会导致像你这样的事情
said in a situation where people are
在人们所处的情况下说
just constantly putting information and
只是不断地提供信息和
how do you know when it's malicious I'm
你怎么知道我什么时候是恶意的
just glad they didn't change the
很高兴他们没有改变
teleprompter and go all Ron Burgundy ha
提词器和 所有Ron Burgundy ha
ha India will ban ecommerce companies
哈印度将禁止电子商务公司
such as Amazon and Walmart owned
如亚马逊和沃尔玛所有
Flipkart from selling products from
Flipkart从销售产品
which they the companies have an equity
他们公司有股权
interest in a statement the government
对政府声明的兴趣
also said that the companies will be
还说公司会
prevented from entering into exclusive
阻止进入专属
agreements with sellers the new rules
与卖方签订新规则
will be applicable from February first
将于2月 1 日起适用
the new regulations follow complaints
新法规遵循投诉
from Indian retailers and traders who
来自印度零售商和贸易商
say the giant ecommerce companies are
比如巨型电子商务公司
using their control over inventory from
使用他们对 库存 的控制
their affiliates and through exclusive
他们的附属公司并通过独家
sales agreements to create an unfair
销售协议造成不公平
marketplace that allows them to sell
允许 他们出售的市场
some products at very low prices the
一些产品以极低的价格
all-india online vendors association in
全印度在线供应商协会
october filed a petition with the
十月提交了一份请愿书 与
antitrust body competition commission of
反垄断机构竞争委员会
india alleging if that amazon favors
印度声称亚马逊是否赞成
merchants that it partly owns the lobby
它部分拥有 大厅的商人
group filed a similar petition against
组提出了类似的请愿 针对
Flipkart in may alleging violations of
Flipkart可能会指控违反
competition rules through preferential
竞争规则通过优惠
treatment for select sellers the new
对新选择的卖家的待遇
rules said that services provided to
规则说提供的服务
vendors on an e-commerce platform and by
电子商务平台 上的供应商 和
that entity's affiliates should be done
该实体的附属机构应该完成
so at an arm's length and in fair and
因此， 在公平 和 公平的情况下
non-discriminatory manner new rules will
新规则将采取非歧视性方式
appease small traders and farmers who
安抚小商贩和农民谁
fear that US companies are making a
担心美国公司 正在 制造
backdoor entry into India's retail
后门进入印度的零售业
market and could squeeze out small
市场可能挤出小
corner shops that dominate Indian route
角落商店主导印度路线
retailing the Confederation of all India
零售全 印度 联邦
traders in a statement said that if the
交易员在声明中说，如果
order is implemented in full then mal
订单是完全实施 然后 mal
practices predatory pricing policies and
实行掠夺性定价政策和
deep discounting by e-commerce players
电子商务玩家的大幅折扣
will no longer occur Amazon India said
将不再发生亚马逊印度说
that it is currently evaluating the new
它目前正在评估新的
rules while Flipkart did not immediately
规则虽然Flipkart没有立即
respond to a request for comment on the
响应请求有关评论
fence about this one you know what so
关于这一个的围栏， 你知道是怎么回事
was I yeah when I saw it I was like I
是的，当我看到它时，我 就像 我 一样
I love the idea of preventing like the
我爱防止类似的想法
big guy going to all the little yes but
大家伙去所有的小小的但是
at the same time I think this is gone
与此同时， 我 认为这已经一去不复返了
too far
太远
in its response like here in Canada
像在加拿大这样的回应
we've got grocery stores you can go to
我们有杂货店你可以去
their website purchase your groceries
他们的网站购买你的杂货
for pickup at the store right it's not
如果在 商店 取货， 那就不是了
right you know
对， 你知道
does that classifies ecommerce and if
这是否对电子商务进行了分类？
you've got a grocery store that now
你有一个杂货店 ， 现在
sells their own brand are they
销售自己的品牌是他们
restricted from doing that in India if
如果被禁止在印度这样做
if the store was in India like how far
如果商店在印度就像多远
does this go because when I read the
这是因为当我读到的时候
definition of what they're talking about
他们所谈论的内容的定义
it's very wide open to just about
这是非常 广泛的，只是 关于 开放
anything yeah and I mean you look at a
什么， 是的，我的 意思是你看 一个
company like coca-cola who's got a ton
像可口可乐公司这样的公司
of subsidiary companies underneath but
下面的子公司但是
they're all under the same corporate
他们都属于同一个公司
umbrella it might be four or five times
伞 可能是四到 五次
removed but under this rule they all
删除但根据这条规则 他们都
apply but what do what what's true about
适用但是做什么才是真实的
that is they have policies in place that
这是他们有政策， 以
you can't have a Pepsi machine next to
你不能有一个百事可乐 机旁
it I know right which is funny it's
它我知道这是有趣 的
tough because like I have to look at
很难因为我必须要看
this one in the perspective of okay this
从好的角度来看这个
is the Indian government protecting the
是印度政府保护的
small marketplace yeah right but in in
小市场是的， 但是在
the terminology it comes across as more
它所涉及的术语更多
like such a controlling mm-hmm like I
像这种控制毫米-HMM等 我
think about if I walk into a grocery
想想我是否 走进 杂货店
store and that grocery store has their
商店 和那家杂货店有他们的
brand like I'm thinking President's
品牌就像我在想总统一样
Choice yeah so if I walk in and there's
选择是的，如果我走进去，那就是
the President's Choice ketchup and
总统的选择番茄酱和
there's the Heinz well they have the
亨氏很好，他们有
loss leaders up at the front all the
所有的 损失领导者都 在前面
press you know like who's to say that
按下 你知道谁会这么说
they can't do
他们做不到
that they own the brands because that's
他们拥有这些品牌，因为那是
their industry Amazon has bought
亚马逊已经购买了他们的行
companies and invested companies and
公司和投资公司 和
created companies in order to sell
创建公司以便出售
products at a better price
产品价格更优惠
by bison Amazon basic stuff quite often
通过bison 亚马逊基本的东西经常
yep
是的
and yeah it it's just the way it is and
并且是啊，这只是 它 的方式 和
it's so tough Sears is out of business I
它是如此艰难的西尔斯是歇业 我 的
know and it's like they were crushed
知道， 就像他们被粉碎一样
but Sears didn't keep up with the
但是西尔斯跟不上了
technology right and so in India I can
技术权利 ，所以在印度 我可以
understand the marketplace is not able
了解市场是不可能的
to keep up with the technology
跟上技术的步伐
necessarily right there are probably
必然是正确的
larger companies definitely are
肯定是大公司
yep that can but the little guys would
是的，但小家伙会这样做
be done for if Sears can be put out of
如果西尔斯可以被淘汰，那就完成了
business
商业
sure absolutely it's this is such a
当然这绝对是这样的
double-edged sword situation and I
双刃剑的情况和我
you're right I think I'm on the fence I
你说得对，我 觉得我在 围栏 我
don't know how I think it's gone too far
不知道我觉得它走得太远了
but I like the notion of it mm-hmm it's
但我喜欢 它 的概念 mm-hmm它
really tough and I think it just boils
非常艰难， 我认为 它只是沸腾
down to this is the time that we are in
到现在为止我们所处的时间
yeah because there's a transition that
是的，因为那是一个转变
has been occurring for the past three
已经发生在过去三年
four years with Amazon becoming the
亚马逊成为四年
biggest retailer in the world it is
世界最大的零售商是
legit how I shop that's it right going
合法的我如何购物，这是正确的
to a store it's like a foreign concept
到商店， 它就像一个外国 概念
to me now I don't I do I go to stores
对我而言我不去做我去商店
but a lot of like Christmas shopping is
但很多 像圣诞购物一样
a perfect example this year and last
今年和最后一个完美的例子
year as well where most of the stuff
一年以及大部分的东西
other than stuff for stockings and
除了丝袜和东西的东西
things like that
这样的事情
yeah bought online and most of that
是的， 在网上买了大部分
through Amazon right I would say like
通过亚马逊，我会说
95% of the gifts I bought this year were
我今年购买的礼物中有 95％ 是
from Amazon yeah yeah mm-hmm what about
从亚马逊呀呀毫米嗯 怎么样
you what are your thoughts on this we're
你对此我有什么看法？
kind of I think we're all three on the
有点我 认为我们都是三个人
fence on this one yeah yeah support it I
在这一个围栏是啊是的支持它我
have absolute support for the little
对小人物有绝对的支持
guys and I understand that market
伙计们，我了解市场
mentality and we need that maybe the
心态 ，我们需要的可能是
government needs to take a different
政府需要采取不同的做法
approach and subsidize the marketplace
接近并补贴市场
subsidize the the little guy and give
补贴小家伙并给予
them incentives to and and capabilities
他们的激励和能力
to
至
flourish if they can't match the prices
如果他们无法匹配价格，那就会蓬勃发展
give them tax breaks I also wonder if
给他们减税， 我也想知道
part of this is country economics
其中一部分是国家经济学
because you look at a country like India
因为你看一个像印度这样的国家
and it's such a massive country and not
它是如此庞大的国家而不是
all areas are equal in their wealth
所有领域 的财富 都是 平等的
distribution or their consumerism so
分配或他们的消费主义如此
maybe there's an element of country
也许有一个国家的元素
specific commerce scenarios that have
具有 特定 商业情景
driven this and so we're looking at it
驱动这一点，所以我们正在寻找 它
from our perspective stuff that way and
从我们的角度来看那种方式和
not understanding this scenario so maybe
也许并不了解这种情况
it's just a matter of North American
这只是 北美问题
ignorance to the true problem I do feel
无知我所感受到的真正问题
that way and that's why I like I'm
那样，那 就是我喜欢 的 原因
awkward in this whole thing because I
这一切都很尴尬，因为我
don't really know what are you watching
真的不 知道你在看什么
our show from India and are impacted
我们来自印度的展会受到了影响
here by this
这里 由该
share your thoughts if you have family
如果你有家人，请分享你的想法
or loved ones in India what are your
或印度的亲人， 你的是什么
thoughts on this particular governance
关于这种特殊治理的想法
yeah we'd love to hear I'd love your
是的，我们很想听到我爱你
your perspective on this the first
你对此的看法第一
autonomous freight train network is
自治区货运列车网络
fully operational on Friday major mining
周五全面开采
corporation Rio Tinto announced that its
公司力拓宣布其公司
auto haul autonomous train system in
汽车 长途列车自治制度
Western Australia had logged more than 1
西澳大利亚州的登记次数 超过1次
million kilometers since July Rio Tinto
自 7月力拓 以来 已达百万公里
now calls its fully operational
现在称其全面运作
autonomous train system the biggest
自动驾驶系统最大
robot in the world the train system
世界上的机器人火车系统
serves fourteen mines that deliver to
供应 14枚水雷，可 提供 给
four port terminals to mines that are
四个端口终端 是地雷
closest to a port terminal will retain
最靠近港口码头的将保留
human engineers because they are very
人类工程师， 因为他们非常
short lines the train system took ten
火车系统需要 十条短线
years to build and cost Rio Tinto nine
年 建成， 耗资力拓9
hundred and sixteen million dollars u.s.
我们一亿一千六百万美元
to implement the trains are remotely
实现列车 远程
monitored by a crew located 1500
由位于1500的船员监控
kilometers away in Perth according to
公里外的珀斯据说
the mining company the autonomous trains
采矿公司自动列车
make sure the rails are clear ahead and
确保导轨 前方 清晰
monitor internal systems set as well
监控内部系统设置
checking for faulty wheels or couplers
检查有故障的车轮或连接器
and bringing the train to a complete
并把火车带到一个完整的
stop if there's a problem
如果有问题就停止
the autonomous train system will allow
自动列车系统将允许
Rio Tinto to cut down on the number
力拓减少了数量
stops at the 2.4 kilometer long
停在 2.4公里长
iron ore hauling trains have to make to
铁矿石牵引火车必须 到达
change drivers prior to the operation of
在 操作 之前 更换驱动程序
the autonomous train system the mining
自动列车系统 的采矿
company shuttle train drivers 1.5
公司 穿梭 火车司机1.5
million kilometers per year due to shift
由于转移 ， 每年每百万公里
changes the average return distance of
改变平均返回距离
these trains is about 800 kilometers
这些火车大约800 公里
with the average journey cycle including
平均 旅程周期包括
loading and dumping taking about 40
装货和倾销大约需要40个
hours additionally the trains will be
还需要几个小时的火车
able to run six percent faster by
能够快6％的速度运行
removing acceleration and braking
消除加速和制动
variations caused by human drivers Rio
由人类司机里约引起的变化
Tinto expects that its auto haul system
Tinto期望 其自动运输系统
will allow it to increase the region's
将允许它增加该地区的
iron ore production capacity by 20
铁矿石产能增加20
million tons
百万吨
that is super that's a neat story yeah
这是超级的，这是一个整洁的 故事是啊
that's a big robot again this is going
这又是一个大机器人
to be two-sided because yeah this is
是双面的，因为是的
gonna mean loss of jobs right absolutely
会意味着失去工作绝对 权
but it's going to be and I feel like
但它会是和我 一样 的感觉
you're driving a train 440 at like it's
你正在驾驶一辆火车440就像它一样
a 40-hour trip you have to be shuttled
一个40小时的旅行，你必须穿梭
to and from because they have to do
来往因为他们必须这样做
shift changes I feel like those jobs
转变我感觉就像那些工作
themselves aren't the ideal job it's
它们本身并不是理想的工作
about having a job I mean like you take
关于有工作 ，我的意思是 像你拿
that mindset you got road construction
你有道路建设的心态
why can't they just put a little rotator
为什么他们不能只是放一点旋转器
on the bottom of a stop sign that flips
翻转停止标志的底部
every you know minute and it's blue you
每次你知道分钟，它是蓝色的 你
know connected to something on the other
知道另一方面与某事有关
side then the sign Turner's have lost
然后那个标志特纳已经输了
their jobs like it's right but I'm
他们的工作是正确的， 但我是
thinking that this will allow for things
认为这将允许 事情
like being the controller like the
像被像控制器
remote remote controller it's like the
远程遥控器它就像
remote and that's operator do you think
你认为 远程和那个操作员
they the the operators 1500 kilometers
他们是运营商1500 公里
away right and presumably a great force
向右走，可能是一股强大的力量
of IT to thwart any attack on this
IT部门阻止 对此的 任何攻击
system right because that would be my
系统权利，因为那将是我的
next fear anything like that I think
接下来我 担心的是恐惧
you're gonna lose one job you're gonna
你要失去一份工作
get another job but a sure Italian job
得到另一份工作， 但 肯定是 意大利工作
different skill set and the person who's
不同的技能和谁 是 人
out of work may not be able to get this
失业可能无法 得到 这个
new job for maybe program
也许是 程序的新工作
the trains or something but the concept
火车或其他东西，但概念
of it is very neat it needs some of that
这是非常整洁，它需要一些
bulk so to speak out of the workload
散装 这么说 出来的工作量
right you know I mean at the end of the
正确的，你知道我的意思是在 的 结束
I mean as a computer guy I mean your
我的 意思是作为一个电脑人 我的意思是你的
automated software that you've created I
你创建的自动化软件我
think you remember you're talking about
想你还记得你在谈论
the AI for a while to help with some of
艾一会儿 ，以帮助一些
your workload your each one Jeff well
你的工作量您的 每一个很好杰夫
but I mean so some of that bulk of his
但我的意思是这样一些 散装的 他
name's Jason he's a real person right
名字是杰森， 他是一个真正的人
okay you can make that can help but it's
好吧，你可以做到这可以帮助，但它是
just like at what cost to the human
就像 人类 付出的代价一样
impact mm-hmm right so and I get both
撞击mm-hmm就这样，我得到了两个
sides but I think it's a neat story I
但我认为这是一个很好的故事
just like the fact that they've
就像 他们 的 事实 一样
automated trains I like it I do made it
自动列车 我喜欢它我做了
faster because humans brake and
更快， 因为人类制动和
accelerate oddly that's interesting too
奇怪地加速这也很有趣
is that yeah what I want to know though
是的 ， 但我想知道的 是 什么
is are there sensors on it for track
是否有传感器在轨道上
runners well it's presumably I mean it's
跑步者很好，这可能是我的意思
monitoring things around it it's gonna
监视它周围的事情会发生
have lidar yeah
有激光雷达是的
once per show and so it's gonna know
每次展示一次，所以它会知道
that there's things moving and you know
有 事情在移动，你知道
if there are kangaroos hopping in front
如果前面有袋鼠跳来跳去的话
of the train they're gonna have to deal
他们将不得不 处理的火车
with that right I just that's just that
有了 这个权利，我 就是这样
they've addressed that sure because
他们已经解决那肯定 是因为
there's nothing more just like sad than
没有什么比悲伤更重要了
to hear that there was of course or is
听到当然 或是
it latonans of course right Oh although
它latonans 当然，对哦，虽然
I will say if that were to be the case
我会说 如果是这样的 话
there isn't a human witness witnessing
目击者没有见证
it now no nice attempt on putting a
它现在没有 很好的尝试
lighter spin on it but you just made it
更轻的旋转它，但你刚刚做到 了
worse you on musk claims to be on track
更糟糕的是 ，麝香声称自己走上正轨
for 2026 Mars colony mission and reveals
2026年火星殖民地的使命和揭示
who will be on board for the first trips
谁将参加第一次旅行
messaging the billionaire on Twitter
在Twitter上传达亿万富翁
musk fan asked how soon will the first
麝香粉丝问第一个会多快
group group go to colonize Mars and musk
小组去火星 和麝香 殖民
replied seven to ten years that's in
回复了七到十年
line with previous estimations from musk
与麝香先前的估计一致
who has said he hopes to launch missions
谁说他希望 发动任务
between 2024 and 2030 musk also recently
最近在2024年至2030年之间麝香
admitted that there was a 70%
承认有70％
chance he himself would move to Mars the
他自己会移动到火星的机会
tesla boss also replied to another
特斯拉老板也 回复了另一个
twitter user who said i only hope the
推特用户谁说我只希望了
first wave of explorers will be poets
第一波探险家将成为诗人
and not real-estate developers must
而不是房地产 开发商必须
respond so was that the initial Mars
回应是最初的火星
colonization flights would be populated
殖民化航班将被填充
with creatives engineers artists and
与创意工程师艺术家和
creators of all kind there is so much to
所有类型的创作者都有很多
build he said it's not the first time
他说这不是第一次
musk has suggested that he'll send
麝香已经暗示他会发送
creative types to space back in 2018
创意类型可追溯到2018年
musk revealed that Japanese billionaire
麝香揭示了日本亿万富翁
art collector yuusaku Misawa would be
艺术收藏家yuusaku Misawa将是
the first passenger on board his SpaceX
SpaceX 上的第一位乘客
trip to the moon the 43 year old
43 岁的月亮之旅
entrepreneur didn't reveal how much he'd
企业家没有透露他有多少
pay for the trip but musk said he has
支付旅行费，但麝香说他有
made a significant deposit on the price
在价格上存了大笔存款
which is a significant price yuusaku
这是一个重要的价格yuusaku
told a thrilled conference in California
在加利福尼亚举行的激动人心的会议
I thought long and hard how valuable it
我 觉得这很有价值
would be to become the first private
将 成为第一个私人
passenger to go to the moon I thought
我想， 乘客去登月
about how this could contribute to world
关于这将如何为世界做出贡献
peace this is my lifelong dream that
和平这是我 一生的梦想
mission to the moon doesn't have a
登月计划不 具有
launch date yet but is expected to take
发布日期，但预计将采取
place within the next few years reaching
在未来几年 内 达到 的地方
the moon is a far easier feet than
月亮 比脚更容易
Musk's planned Mars missions
马斯克计划的火星任务
the billionaire recently admitted early
这位亿万富翁最近很早就承认了
travelers have a good chance of dying on
旅行者很有可能死亡
the way spacex is currently working on a
spacex目前正在研究的方式
vessel named starship it's believed to
这艘名为starship 的 船只被 认为是
that starship will be able to make the
那艘星舰将能够成功
voyage to Mars with humans on board
与人类 搭乘火箭前往火星
within the next seven years spacex hopes
在未来七年内， spacex希望如此
to eventually create spacefaring
最终创造航天
civilization which would include Martian
文明包括火星人
colonies populated by humans tickets for
人口居住的殖民地门票
the trip would cost around a couple
这次旅行将耗费 大约一双
hundred thousand dollars according to
据说十万美元
musk musk however reckons that living on
然而，麝香麝香认为生活在麝香上
Mars won't be cheery and certainly not a
火星不会是愉快的，当然也不是
luxury retreat your probability of dying
豪华撤退你 死亡 的 概率
on Mars is much higher than on earth
在火星上远远高于地球
the billionaire explained he also said
这位亿万富翁解释说他也说过
that early Mars colonists would be
早期的火星殖民者会
working nonstop to build the base and
不间断地工作以 建立基地和
this would leave not much time for
这将留下不多的时间
leisure
闲暇
and even after doing all this it's a
甚至在完成所有这些之后 它就是一个
very harsh environment he said and even
他说 甚至是非常恶劣的环境
if you survive the trip to Mars it's
如果你在火星旅行中幸存下来了
entirely possible that you'll never be
完全有可能， 你永远 是
able to return to Earth there's a good
能够 返回 地球 有一个很好的
chance you die there Musquin
你有机会死在Musquin
said you can think come back you can
说你可以想想回来你可以
come back but we're not sure now that
回来但我们现在还不确定
does sound like an escape hatch for rich
听起来像 富人 的逃生舱
people so I love this story on so many
人们所以我很喜欢这个故事
levels of stupidity what I do appreciate
愚蠢的水平我很欣赏
his honesty yes well it's true yes I
他的诚实是的，这是真的，是的， 我
can't believe that it's actually going
我不敢相信它真的 会发生
to happen like I'm that soon you can't
就像 我很快就会 发生的 那样
believe like you don't believe or you
相信你不相信或你
can't believe like oh my harshly I mean
我不敢相信哦，我的意思是严厉的
do you look at his track record and you
你看他的跟踪 记录 吗？
know they he's a visionary
知道他们是一个有远见的人
obviously but he has the capabilities he
很明显，但他有能力
projects you know where I like to
你知道我喜欢的项目
over-promised under promise and over
在承诺 下 过度承诺
perform right geez hands to over promise
执行正确的geez手以过度 承诺
and under perform so when he you know
如果你知道的话，那就在表演中
announces the new Tesla and then it
宣布新的特斯拉，然后它
takes several years before it's you know
需要 几年才能 知道
beyond the the day I just don't know
超出我不知道的那一天
that it's going to happen but so there's
它会发生但是就是这样
that doubt because of his track record
因为他的 记录而怀疑
but at the same time I know that if
但与此同时， 我知道 如果
anyone can do it it is Iron Man I mean
任何人都可以做到这 就是钢铁侠我的意思
Elon Musk space that's true he did what
伊隆马斯克的 空间 是真的，他做了什么
I find interesting about this story
我觉得这个故事很有趣
though is the fact that we don't know
虽然事实是我们不知道
the long-term impacts of space residency
空间 居住的长期影响
sure I mean we've had people on the
我的意思是说我们有人参加
International Space Station for extended
国际空间站 延长
periods of time I mean look at the the
一段时间我的意思是看看
twins one wasn't one was an astronaut
双胞胎一个 不是一个宇航员
one was not he the brother came back
一个不是他 兄弟回来了
from space and genetically he has
从太空和他的遗传
changed from his brother mm-hm
改变了他的兄弟 mm-hm
so we don't know what this is going to
所以我们不知道这是怎么回事
mean if it's like we're going to send
是否意味着我们要 发送
you to Mars you get there in a year and
你去 火星，你一年到达那里
you may never come back what's five
你可能永远不会回来五点
years impact
年影响
I think before we start jumping at Mars
我想在开始跳火星之前
put something on the moon where things
把 东西放在月球上的东西
go bad you're only three days away it
变坏你 只有三天了
sounds like that's what he's doing
听起来就像他正在做的那样
but at the same time he's being really a
但与此同时他真的是一个
downer to his own program by being
屈服于他自己的 计划
realistic and honest to say you know you
说实话，老实说你了解你
can pay to go to Mars I'll fly you there
可以付钱去 火星 我会把你 带到 那里
probably gonna die well that's has
可能会死得很好
nothing to do with his product that's
与他的产品无关
the environment of space I mean that'd
太空环境我的意思是'
be like hey we can get you a wetsuit
就像嘿，我们可以给你一个潜水服
that allows you to swim with great white
这可以让你和白色一起游泳
sharks but there's a risk you could get
鲨鱼， 但你可能会有风险
eaten that's not but this is progress
吃了那 不是，但这 是进步
that is stupidity there is a fair chance
那是愚蠢 有一个公平的 机会
if you decide to go to Mars you know
如果你决定去 火星， 你 知道
you're not coming back sure you know it
你不会回来 确定你知道它
like you know it you've lived your life
就像你知道的那样，你过着自己的生活
in your soul you know you're not coming
在你的灵魂中，你 知道你不会来
back to earth even if they say that
即使他们这样说，也要回到地球上
there's a chance there is no chance
有机会 没有机会
there is you might get to Mars and live
你可能会去火星生活
on Mars for a blip but there is one
在火星上昙花一现但有一个
benefit to go into Mars what is that
有利于进入火星那是什么
you're not gonna have to shovel the snow
你不必铲雪
yeah you might just quickly according to
是的，你可能很快就会根据
coin gecko here's how the crypto market
硬币壁虎在这里是如何加密市场
looked as of 1800 hours Eastern Time on
截至东部时间 1800小时
Wednesday January the 2nd 2019 Bitcoin
星期三1月2019年2月 比特币
is up gaining 165 dollars and 62 cents
上涨165美元和62美分
US and is presently at three thousand
美国目前在三千
eight hundred and fifty five dollars and
八百 五 十五 美元
six cents litecoin similarly up and
六美分莱特币同样上涨
going up by three dollars and eighty
涨了三美元八十美元
three cents us hitting thirty two
我们打三十二分三分钱
dollars and seventy six cents aetherium
美元和 七十六美分的aetherium
likewise up fifty three dollars and 34
同样高达五十三美元和34美元
cents at one hundred and fifty three
一百五十 三美分
dollars and thirty cents remember three
美元和三十美分记住三个
weeks ago is that only $99.99 Manero
几个星期前 只有99.99美元的 Manero
also gaining the slider game at fifty
也获得了 50 的滑块 游戏
one dollars and forty nine cents as this
一个美元和 49美分 ，因为这
week's where it hit stellite looking at
一周的时候，它 看到 了stellite
the little guys is also on its way up at
这些小家伙也在上路
two dollar not two dollars pardon me I
两美元不是 两美元我原谅我
keep doing that
继续这样做
two point three one ten thousandth of a
二点三一 十千分之一
cent
一分钱
I need if stellite was $2 turtle coin
如果stellite是$ 2乌龟硬币 我 需要
and even littler gay 1.2 for 10
甚至更小的同性恋1.2
thousandths of a cent also gaining point
千分之一美分 也越来越重要
seven eight ten thousandth of a cent
七八分之一万分之一
remember that cryptocurrency is always
记住加密货币总是如此
changing the market is always open and
改变市场总是开放的
it's always volatile so be careful and
它总是不稳定所以要小心
be mindful of that fact
要注意这个事实
big thanks to Roy W Nash in our
非常感谢罗伊W¯¯纳什在我们
community of viewers for submitting
观众社区提交
stories to us this week thanks for
本周故事给我们感谢
watching the category-five TV newsroom
看 五类电视 新闻编辑室
don't forget to Like and subscribe for
别忘了喜欢和订阅
all your tech news with a slight Linux
所有 科技 新闻 都有轻微的 Linux
bias and for more free content be sure
偏见和更多免费内容确定
to check out our website from the
从中 查看我们的网站
category-five TV newsroom I'm Sasha
五类电视 新闻编辑室我是 Sasha
Rickman and I'm Robbie Ferguson and I'm
瑞克曼和我是罗比弗格森而我
Jeff Weston thank you so much for being
杰夫韦斯顿非常感谢你的存在
here again with us this week hope you've
本周 再次 与 我们在一起希望你们
enjoyed the show happy new year and
欣赏演出新年快乐 ，
here's to 2019 being awesome for you
这是2019年对你来说真棒
your family your loved ones and just
你的家人你的亲人和公正
all-around looking forward to a great
全能期待 一个伟大的
year ahead have a great week everyone
未来一年每个人都有一个美好的一周
[Music]
[音乐]
[Applause]
[掌声]
you
您